today we're going to go over these four major software packages that people
오늘 우리는이 네 개의 주요 소프트웨어 패키지를 통해 갈거야 그 사람들
commonly used as usual a couple administrative things the milestones
일반적으로 보통 몇 관리자 가지 이정표로 사용
were actually do last week so hopefully return the men will try to take a look
실제로 그렇게 희망을 살펴하려고합니다 남자를 반환 지난 주 않는 한
at those this week also remember that assignment 3 the final assignment is
최종 할당은 3 사람들에 이번 주 또한 할당을 기억
gonna be due on Wednesday so and you guys done already
거야 그래서 수요일에 기인하고 너희들은 아직
ok that's that's good then you have late days you should be fine
확인 그건 그 다음 당신은 당신이 잘 늦게 일을해야했습니다 좋은
another another thing that I should point out is that if you're actually
내가 지적해야 다른 또 다른 한가지는 당신이 실제로 있다면
planning on using Terminal for your projects which i think a lot of you are
내가 당신을 많이 생각 프로젝트에 대한 터미널을 사용할 계획
then make sure you you're backing up your code and data and things off of
당신은 당신이 떨어져 코드 및 데이터 물건을 백업하고 있는지 확인
paternal instances every once in a while we've had some problems where the
아버지의 경우는 가끔씩 우리는 어떤 데 문제 했어
instances will crash randomly and in most cases the terminal folks have been
인스턴스는 무작위로 충돌하고 대부분의 경우 단말기 사람들은왔다
able to get the data back but it sometimes takes a couple days and
데이터를 다시 얻을 수 있지만 때로는 몇 일이 소요 및
there's been a couple of cases where actually people lost data because it was
이 때문에 사람들이 손실 된 데이터를 실제 사례 몇 가지가있었습니다
just on terminal and that crashed so I think if you are planning to use
그냥 터미널에 그 당신이 사용하려는 경우 내가 생각하는 그래서 추락
terminal then make sure that you have some alternative backup strategy for
단말기는 당신이 어떤 다른 백업 전략을 가지고 있는지 확인
your code and your data like I said today we're talking about these poor
코드와 나는 같은 데이터는 우리가이 불쌍한 대해 얘기 밝혔다
software packages that are commonly used for a deep learning cafe torch piano and
일반적으로 깊은 학습 카페 토치 피아노에 사용되는 소프트웨어 패키지와
tensor flow and as a little bit of disclaimer at the beginning I felt like
텐서 흐름과 내가 같은 느낌이 처음에 부인의 조금으로
personally I've mostly worked with cafe and torch so those the ones that I know
개인적으로 나는 주로 내가 아는 그 사람 때문에 카페와 성화와 함께 일했습니다
the most about I'll do my best to give you a good flavor for the others as well
I에 대한 가장 당신에게 다른 사람에 대한 좋은 맛을뿐만 아니라 제공하기 위해 최선을 다하겠습니다
but just throwing that disclaimer out there so the first one is cafe we saw in
하지만 단지 첫 번째, 그래서 거기에 그 부인을 던지는 것은 우리가 본 카페입니다
the last lecture that really cafe sprung out of this paper at berkeley that was
정말 카페이었다 버클리에서 본 논문에서 튀어 마지막 강의
trying to a re-employment Alex NAT and Alex features for other things and since
재 고용 알렉스 NAT와 알렉스하려고하는 것은 다른 것들과 이후 기능
then kathy has really grown into a really really popular widely used
다음 캐시는 정말 널리 사용되는 정말 인기로 성장했다
package for especially convolutional neural networks so Cafe is from Berkeley
카페 버클리에서 그래서 특히 길쌈 신경망을위한 패키지
that I think a lot of you people have no no
난 당신이 많은 사람들은 더없는이 생각
and it's mostly written in C++ and there is actually buying things for a cafe so
그것은 대부분 C ++로 작성 실제로 카페에 대한 일이 구입되어,
you can access the nets and whatnot in Python in Matlab that are super useful
당신은 매우 유용하다 matlab에 파이썬에서 그물과 이것 저것에 액세스 할 수 있습니다
and in general cafes really widely used and it's really really good if you just
일반 카페에서 정말 널리 사용하고 그냥 경우는 정말 정말 좋은
want to train sort of standard feedforward convolutional networks and
일종의 표준 피드 포워드 컨볼 루션 네트워크를 훈련하고 싶은
actually Cafe is somewhat different than the others
실제로 카페는 다른 사람보다 약간 다르다
other frameworks in this respect you can actually trained big powerful models and
이 점에서 다른 프레임 워크는 당신이 실제로 큰 강력한 모델을 훈련하고
kept a without writing any code yourself so for example the ResNet image
예제 ResNet 이미지를 그래서 어떤 코드를 직접 작성하지 않고 유지
classification model that one image that one everything last year you can
분류 모델을 하나의 이미지 하나 다 작년에 당신이 할 수있는 그
actually trained to resonate using cafe without writing any code which is pretty
실제로 꽤 임의의 코드를 작성하지 않고 카페를 사용하여 공진 훈련
amazing so the most but the most important tip when you're working with
놀라운 가장 그러나 당신이 작업하는 가장 중요한 팁 그래서
cafe is that the documentation is not as sometimes out of date and not always
카페 설명서를 항상 최신 상태로 때때로되지 않고하지 않는 것이있다
perfect so you need to not be afraid to just dive in there and read the source
완벽한 그래서 당신은 단지 거기에 다이빙 소스를 읽을 두려워하지 필요
code yourself it's C++ so hopefully you can read that and understand it but in
그것은 ++ C의 너무 잘하면 당신이 그것을 읽고 이해 만에 할 수 있습니다 자신을 코드
general the C++ code that they have interface is pretty well structured
그들이 인터페이스가 일반 C ++ 코드를 꽤 잘 구성되어
pretty well organized and pretty easy to understand so if you have doubts about
꽤 잘 조직하고 대한 의심이있는 경우 아주 쉽게 그렇게 이해하기
how things work in cafe you do your best bet is just to go on get up and read the
일이 카페에서 일하는 당신은 어떻게 당신의 가장 좋은 건에 가서 일어나서을 읽을 그냥 할
source code so Cafe is this huge big project with Mike probably thousands
카페 그래서 소스 코드는 아마 수천 마이크와 함께이 거대한 큰 프로젝트입니다
tens of thousands of lines of code and it's a little bit scary to understand
수십 줄의 코드 수천하고 이해하기 무서운 약간의
how everything fits together but there's really four major classes in cafe that
모든 것을 함께 맞는하지만 카페에서 정말 네 개의 주요 클래스를 거기에 어떻게
you need to know about the first one is a blob so blobs army store all of your
첫 번째 일에 대해 알 필요가있는 얼룩 때문에 모든 군대 저장소를 모양 당신의
data and your weight and your activations in the network so these
데이터와 무게와 네트워크에서 활성화 그래서 이러한
blobs are things in the network so your weights are have blocked are your rates
모양은 그래서 당신의 무게가 차단 한있는 네트워크의 것들 당신의 비율은
are stored in a blob your data which would be like your pixel values are
블롭에 저장되어있는 데이터는 픽셀 값처럼 될 것이다있다
stored in a blob and your labels your wife or stored in a blob and also all of
블롭에 저장 레이블 당신의 아내 또는 BLOB에 저장된 모든의
your intermediate activations will also be stored in blobs so blobs are these
모양이입니다 귀하의 중간 정품 인증은 모양에 저장됩니다
and dimensional tensors sort of like you've seen an umpire accepted they
과 차원 텐서는 일종의 당신이 본 것 같은 심판은 허용
actually have four copies of a non-dimensional tenser inside they have
그들이 가진 내부 실제로 무 차원 tenser 네 사본을
data
데이터
data version of the tensor which is storing the actual raw data and they
실제 원시 데이터하고 저장하는 텐서의 데이터 버전
also have a parallel thing but parallel 10 circled deaths that cafe uses to
또한 카페가 사용하는 병렬 일을 가지고 있지만 10 평행 죽음을 원
store gradients with respect to that data and that gives you two and then you
저장소는 데이터에 대한 그라디언트 그것은 당신에게 당신에게 두 가지를 제공하고
actually have four because there's a CPU and GPU version of each of those things
그런 것들의 각각의 CPU와 GPU 버전이 있기 때문에 실제로 사를
so you have data types of CPU and GPU there's actually four and dimensional
그래서 당신은 CPU의 데이터 유형이 있고 GPU 실제로 사 및 치수있다
tents are superb lob the next important class that you need to know about and
텐트 당신이 알아야 할 그 다음 중요한 클래스 로브 뛰어난이며,
cafes the lair and a larry is sort of a function from similar to the ones who
은신처를 카페와 래리는 것과 유사한에서 함수의 일종이다 사람
wrote on the hallmarks that receives some input blobs catcalls inputs bottoms
일부 입력 모양을받는 특징에 글을 입력 바닥을 야유
and then produces output blobs that kept a hole stop lobs the idea is that your
다음 구멍 정지를 유지 출력 모양을 생각한다는 것입니다 LOB를 생성하여
lair will receive pointers to the bottom blobs with the data Rd filled in and
은신처가 채워 데이터 (RD)와 바닥 모양에 포인터를 받게되며
then it'll also receive a pointer to the top blobs and it'll end in Fort
다음은 상단 모양에 대한 포인터를 받게됩니다 그리고 포트에 겁니다
passionately expected to fill in the values for the data elements of your top
열정적으로 상위의 데이터 요소의 값을 입력 할 것으로 예상
blogs on the back road past the layers will compute radiance sable expects to
층을지나 다시 도로에 블로그 래디언스 검은 담비가 기대 계산합니다
receive a pointer to the top jobs with the gradients and the activation spilled
기울기와 상부 작업에 대한 포인터를 수신하고 활성화 쏟
an and then they'll also receive a pointer to the bottom blobs until
를 사용하며 그들은 또한 바닥 모양에 대한 포인터까지를 받게됩니다
ingredients for the bottoms and Blair is this a pretty well structured abstract
재료 바닥과 블레어 총리는이 추상 꽤 잘 구성되어
class that you can go and I had to have the the links for the source file here
클래스 당신은 갈 수 있고 내가 여기에 소스 파일에 대한 링크를했다 그
and there's a lot of some classes that implement different types of theirs and
그리고 그들의의 다른 유형을 구현하는 몇 가지 클래스가 많이있다 및
like I said a common cap a problem there's no really good list of all the
같은 나는 일반적인 캡이 문제가 모든 전혀 정말 좋은 목록이 없습니다 말했다
lair types you pretty much just need to look at the code and see what types of
유형의 은신처 당신은 거의 그냥 코드를보고 어떤 종류를 볼 필요가
CPP files there are the next thing you need to know about is a natural so and
CPP 파일은 자연 있도록 당신이 알아야 할 다음 일은있다
that just combines multiple heirs and that is basically directed acyclic graph
그것은 단지 다수의 상속인을 결합하고는 기본적으로 비순환 그래프에 관한 것이다
of layers and is responsible for running the forward and backward methods of the
층과하면의 전후 방법을 실행하기위한 책임
layers in the correct order so this is you probably don't need to touch this
올바른 순서 층은 그래서 이것은 당신은 아마이 터치하지 않아도된다
class ever yourself but it's kind of nice to look at to get a flavour of how
자신 만이에 가지 좋은 볼의 어느 클래스는 방법의 맛을 얻을 수
everything fits together in the final class that you need to know about a
모든 당신이 알아야 할 마지막 클래스에서 함께 맞는
solver so the solver is you know we have this thing called solver on the homework
솔버가 솔버 있도록 우리가 숙제 해결사이라는 것을 알고
that was really inspired by capping a somersault or is intended to dip into
그 정말 재주 넘기를 캡에서 영감을받은 나에 찍어하기위한 것입니다
the net
순
run the next forward and backward on data actually update
실제로 업데이트 데이터의 다음 전후 실행할
owners of the network and handle checkpointing and resuming from
네트워크와 핸들 검사 점과에서 다시 시작의 소유자
checkpoints and all that sort of stuff and in cafe solver is this abstract
체크 포인트 및 물건의 카페 해결사의 모든 종류의이 추상입니다
class and different update rules are implemented by different subclasses so
클래스와 다른 갱신 규칙은 다른 서브 클래스에 의해 구현된다 그래서
there is for example stochastic gradient descent solver there's an atom bomb ass
예를 확률 그라데이션 하강을 위해 존재하는 것은 해석 원자 폭탄 엉덩이있다
problem-solver all of that sort of stuff and again just to see what kinds of
문제 해결사 다시 물건의 종류의 모든과는 어떤 종류를 볼 수 있습니다
options are available you should look at the source code for this kind of gives
옵션을 제공합니다 당신은 이런 종류의 소스 코드를 찾아야한다 사용할 수 있습니다
you a nice overview of how these things all fit together that this whole thing
당신이 일 모두가이 모든 일이 있음을 함께 맞는 방법의 좋은 개요
on the right would be done at the net contains in the green boxes blobs each
인터넷에서 할 것이다 오른쪽 녹색 상자에 포함 각을 얼룩
blog contains data and texts the red boxes are layers that are connecting
블로그는 데이터를 포함하고 빨간색 상자가 연결되어있는 층이다 텍스트
blocks together and the whole thing would get optimized for the Psalter so
함께 블록과 모든 일이 시편에 최적화 얻을 것이다 그래서
cafe makes heavy use of this funny thing called protocol buffers any of you guys
카페 프로토콜이라는 재미있는 것은 많이 사용 너희들의 버퍼 수
ever in turn to Google after numbers you guys know about this bomb but protocol
이제까지 숫자 후 구글에 다시 너희들은이 폭탄 그러나 프로토콜에 대해 알고
poppers are this almost like a binary strongly typed JSON I sort of like to
권총은 거의 이진 강하게 나는 종류의에 같은 JSON을 입력처럼 이쪽
think about it that are used very widely inside google first utilizing data to
구글이 처음에 데이터를 이용하여 내부에 매우 널리 사용되는 그것에 대해 생각
death over the network so protocol buffers there's this . profile that
네트워크를 통해 죽음은 그래서 프로토콜이있다 버퍼링한다. 그 프로필
defines the different kinds of feels that different types of objects how so
서로 다른 객체의 형태를 어떻게 그렇게 느낌의 종류를 정의
in this example there's a person has a name and I D and an email and this lives
이 예에서 사용자는 이름 및 ID 및 이메일이 생명을 가지고있을 것
in a top profile . profiles
최고의 프로필입니다. 프로필
given to find a type of a class and you can actually see realize instances to
클래스의 유형을 찾기 위해 주어진 당신은 실제로에 인스턴스를 실현 볼 수 있습니다
human readable . total txt files so for example this fills in the name it gives
사람이 읽을. 예를 들어 이것은주는 이름 총 TXT 파일을 채우고 있으므로
you the idea gives you the email and this is an instance of a person that can
당신은 아이디어가 당신에게 이메일을 제공하고이 사람의 인스턴스입니다 수
be saved into this text file then product includes this compiler that
이 텍스트 파일로 저장 한 후 제품이 컴파일러를 포함
actually lets you generate classes in various programming languages to access
실제로 액세스 다양한 프로그래밍 언어에서 클래스를 생성 할 수 있습니다
these data types you can after running photobook compiler this profile it
당신이 할 수있는 이러한 데이터 형식 포토 북 컴파일러를 실행 한 후이 그것을 프로필
produces classes that you can import in Java and C C++ and Python and go and
당신은 자바와 C C에 가져 ++과 파이썬과 갈 수있는 클래스를 생성
just about everything so actually cafe makes why do you say these probe of
모든 그래서 실제로 카페가 있습니다 단지에 대해 왜 이러한 프로브를 말합니까
these protocol buffers and they use them to store pretty much everything and
이러한 프로토콜 버퍼 그들은 거의 모든 것을 저장을 사용하여
Kathy so like I said to understand you need to read the code understand cafe
캐시는 내가 말했듯 있도록 카페를 이해하는 코드를 읽을 필요가 이해하기
and cafe has this one giant file called cafe dark road
카페이 하나의 거대한 파일이라는 카페 어두운 도로가
though they just defines all of the protocol buffer types that are used in
그들은 단지에서 사용되는 프로토콜 버퍼 유형 모두를 정의하지만
cafe this is a gigantic file its I think it's a couple thousand lines long but
카페는이 나는 그것이 몇 생각의 거대한 파일 만 라인 긴하지만
it's actually pretty well documented and is I think the most up-to-date
실제로 꽤 잘 문서화 그리고 내가 가장 최신의 생각입니다
documentation of what are the lair types are what the options for those layers
은신처 유형이 무엇인지의 문서는 어떤 이들 계층에 대한 옵션입니다
are how you specify every all the options for solvers and layers and
당신이 솔버 및 레이어와마다 모든 옵션을 지정하는 방법입니다
that's not all bad so I really encourage you to check out this file and read
그 때문에 난 정말이 파일을 체크 아웃하고 읽어 보시기 바랍니다 모든 나쁘지 않다
through it if you have any questions about how things work in cafe and just
일이 카페 단지 어떻게 작동하는지 그것을 통해 당신에 대한 질문이있는 경우
give you a flavour on my left ear this shows you this defines than a parameter
이 매개 변수보다 정의이 당신을 보여줍니다 당신이 내 왼쪽 귀에서 맛을 제공
which is the type of protocol buffer that cafe uses to represent an axe and
이는 카페 도끼를 나타내는 데 사용 프로토콜 버퍼의 종류 및
on the right is this solver parameter which used to represent solvers so that
오른쪽 해법을 나타내는 데,이 해석 파라미터 있도록
perimeter of the solver promoter for example takes a reference to a net and
예를 들어 솔버 프로모터의 경계가 그물에 대한 참조를 취하고
it also includes things like learning rate and how often to check point and
또한 학습 속도와 빈도 점을 확인하는 방법과 같은 것들을 포함
other things like that right so when you're working in cafe actually it's
당신이 카페에서 작업 할 때 바로 그래서 실제로 있다는 같은 다른 것들
pretty cool you don't need to write any code in order to train models so when
정말 멋진 그렇게 할 때 모델을 양성하기 위해 코드를 작성할 필요가 없습니다
working with cafe you generally have this four-step process so first you will
카페 작업 당신은 일반적으로 당신은 그래서 먼저이 4 단계 프로세스를
convert your data and especially if you just happen image classification problem
데이터를 변환하고 그냥 이미지 분류 문제가 발생할 경우 특히
you don't have to write any code for this you just use one of the existing
당신은 단지 기존 중 하나를 사용이를 위해 당신은 어떤 코드를 작성할 필요가 없습니다
binary Kappa ships with Daniel define your your file that you'll do by just
다니엘 이진 카파 배는 방금로 할 것이다 당신의 파일을 정의
writing or editing one of these proteins Daniel define your solver which again
작성 또는 편집이 단백질 다니엘 중 하나는 다시 해석을 정의
will just live in Provo txt txt file that you can just work within a text
단지 프로보 TXT TXT 파일에 살 것이다 당신은 텍스트 내에서 작동 할 수
editor and then you'll pass all of these things to this existing binary to train
편집기 다음은 훈련이 기존 바이너리에이 일을 모두 통과합니다
the model and battle spit out your train kept a model to test that you can then
모델과 전투는 기차가 그 다음에 할 수 있는지 테스트하는 모델을 계속 뱉어
use for other things so even if you want to train ResNet on image that you could
당신은 당신이 할 수 이미지에 ResNet 훈련을 할 경우에도, 그래서 다른 것들에 사용
just follow the simple procedure and train a giant network without writing
그냥 간단한 절차를 따르 쓰기없이 거대한 네트워크를 훈련
any code that's really cool and so step one generally only to convert your data
정말 멋진 등 만 데이터를 변환하기 위해 일반적으로 한 단계 코드
so cafe uses I know we've talked a little bit about html5 as format for
그래서 카페 나는 우리가 형식으로 HTML5에 대해 조금 얘기했습니다 알고 사용
storing pixels on desk continuously and then reading from them efficiently but
지속적으로 책상에 픽셀을 저장하고 효율적으로 읽는하지만,
by default Kathy uses this other file format called LM TV so there's asked if
경우가 물었다 그래서 기본적으로 캐시는 LM TV라는이 다른 파일 형식을 사용
you if all you have is a bunch of images each image with a label then you can
당신이 당신이 가진 모든 레이블이 각 이미지 다음 이미지의 무리 인 경우 당신은 할 수
call lol
롤 호출
cafe just has a script to convert that whole dataset into a giant alamoudi be
카페는 수 거대한 alamoudi에 그 전체 데이터 집합을 변환하는 스크립트가 있습니다
you can use for training so Jen just to give you an idea of the way it's this is
젠은 당신에게 방법의 아이디어를 제공 할 수 있도록이는 그것의 훈련을 위해 사용할 수 있습니다
really easy you just create a text file that has the path to your images and
당신은 당신의 이미지에 대한 경로를 가진 텍스트 파일을 작성 정말 쉽고
separated by the label and you just passenger kept a script wait a couple
라벨로 구분하고 그냥 승객은 스크립트가 몇 기다려 유지
hours if your data sets big giant IMDB file on disk and if you're working with
시간 데이터가 디스크에 큰 거대한 IMDB 파일을 설정하고있는 경우에는 작업하는 경우
something else like HBO five then you'll have to create yourself probably so cafe
HBO 오 같은 뭔가 다른 당신은 아마 카페 그래서 자신을 만들어야합니다
does actually have a couple of options to reading data and there's this date on
실제로 데이터를 읽는 몇 가지 옵션을 가지고이 날짜에있다 않습니다
their window dato mayor for protection and actually can read from HDL 5 and
자신의 윈도우 다토 보호를위한 시장 실제로는 HDL 5에서 읽을 수 있습니다
there's an option for reading stuff directly from memory that's especially
특히의 직접 메모리에서 읽기 물건에 대한 옵션이있다
useful with Python interface but at least in my point of view all of these
이 모든 파이썬 인터페이스하지만 내 관점에서 적어도 유용
types of other methods of reading and data to campaign are a little bit
캠페인에 읽기 및 데이터의 다른 방법의 종류가 조금 있습니다
second-class citizens in the cafe ecosystem and Ellen DBA is really the
두 번째 수준의 카페 생태계에서 시민과 엘렌 DBA 정말입니다
easiest thing to work with so if you can you should probably try to convert your
가장 쉬운 것은 당신이 당신이 아마 변환을 시도해야 할 수 있습니다 그래서 만약 작동하는 방법
data into mp3 format with so step 24 campaign is to define your object so
그래서 24 캠페인 단계와 mp3 형식으로 데이터가 있으므로 객체를 정의하는 것입니다
like I said he'll just to write a big promo txt to find your not so here this
같은 나는 그가 그냥하지 그래서 여기에이를 찾기 위해 큰 프로모션 TXT를 작성하는 것입니다 말했다
is this just a simple model for logistic regression you can see that I did not
로지스틱 회귀 분석이 단순한 모델 당신은 내가하지 않았다 것을 알 수있다
follow my own advice and I'm reading data out of an HDL 5 file here then I
내 자신의 조언을 따라 난 다음 여기에 HDL (5) 파일에서 데이터를 읽고 있어요
have a fully connected layer which is called inner product and Cathay than
내적 및 캐세이보다라고 완전히 연결 층을
their rights that's fully connected lair tells you the number of classes and how
완전히 은신처를 연결되어 자신의 권리는 당신에게 수업 방법의 수를 알려줍니다
to initialize the values and then I have a soft max loss function that read the
값을 초기화하고 내가 읽어 부드러운 최대 손실 함수를합니다
labels and produces loss ingredients from the opposite elected leader so a
라벨과는 반대 선출 된 리더에서 손실 성분을 생성하므로
couple things to point out about this file are that one every layer typically
이 파일에 대해 지적하는 몇 가지 있습니다 일반적으로 한 모든 층이
include some blogs which to store the data and the gradients in the weights
가중치의 데이터를 저장하기 위해 약간의 블로그와 기울기를 포함
and the layers blobs and Bellaire itself typically have the same name that can be
그리고 층의 모양과 벨레 자체가 일반적으로 할 수있는 같은 이름을 가진
a little bit confusing another thing is that a lot of these layers will have two
다른 일을 혼란 조금 이들 층의 많은이있을 것입니다
blobs 14 weight and 14 bias and actually in this network right in here you'll
바로 당신이거야 여기에이 네트워크에 실제로 14 무게 14 바이어스와 모양
find the learning rates for those two blobs so that's learning rate and
즉 학습 속도가 그래서 그 두 모양의 학습 속도를 찾아
regularization for both the way
방법 모두 정규화
bias of that later another thing to note is that to specify the number of output
참고로 나중에 또 하나의 바이어스는 출력의 수를 지정하는 것입니다
classes is just the number
클래스는 단지 숫자입니다
output on this fully connected lair perimeter and finally the quick and
이 완전히 연결 은신처 주변에 출력하고 마지막으로 신속하고
dirty way to freeze layers and cafe is just to set the learning rate 204 that
레이어와 카페를 동결 더러운 방법은 학습 속도 (204)를 설정하는 것입니다
for the blobs associated to that way it's our biases another thing to point
그런 식으로 연결된 모양에 대한 우리의 편견 지적하는 또 다른 일이
out is that for ResNet and other large models like Google that this can get
밖으로 구글과 같은 ResNet 및 기타 대형 모델이 얻을 수 있다는 것입니다
really out of hand really quickly so cafe doesn't really let you define like
정말 정말 빨리 손에서 카페 정말 당신처럼 정의 할 수 없습니다 있도록
composition ality so for ResNet they just repeat the same pattern over and
조성의 ality ResNet을 위해 그들은 단지 동일한 패턴을 통해 반복되도록
over and over in the Pro txt file so the ResNet proto txt is almost 7,000 lines
반복해서 ResNet의 프로토 TXT 그래서 프로 txt 파일에 거의 7,000 선이다
long so you could write that by hand but interim practice people tend to write
당신이 손으로 그것을 쓸 수 있지만 중간 연습 사람들이 쓰는 경향이 긴 있도록
little python script to generate these things automatically so that's that's a
그가가의 그래서 작은 파이썬 스크립트는 자동으로이 일을 생성하는
little bit gross you out if you want to find to a network rather than starting
네트워크에 찾을 것이 아니라 시작하려면 약간의 총 당신을
from scratch then you'll typically download some existing product ext and
처음부터 당신은 일반적으로 몇 가지 기존 제품 내선을 다운로드 할 수 있습니다 및
some existing weights file and work from there so the way you should think about
일부 기존 무게 파일과 작업 거기에서 그래서 당신이 생각해야하는 방법
it is that the product txt file that we've seen here before it defines the
우리가 여기에 본 적이 제품 txt 파일이이를 정의하기 전에 것입니다
architecture of the network and Mendel the preacher and weights live in this
설교자와 무게이 살고있는 네트워크와 멘델의 아키텍처
cafe model file that's a binary thing and you can't really inspected but the
진 일이 그리고 당신이 정말로 검사를하지만, 수 없습니다 카페 모델 파일
way it works that's basically key-value pairs where it matches name where the
그것은 그 작동 방법은 이름 위치를 일치 기본적으로 키 - 값 쌍의
inside the cafe model it matches these names that are scoped to Lares so this
카페 모델 안에이 때문에 가정의 수호신으로 범위가 이들의 이름과 일치
xc70 weight with the would-be though the way its corresponding to this final
그런데 그가 마지막에 해당 불구과 XC70 무게는-것
fully connected layer and Alex not so then when you want to find you on your
완전히 연결 층과 알렉스하지 그래서 다음에 당신을 찾을 때
own data when you start up cafe and you load a model and a product ext
자신의 데이터는 카페를 시작하고 당신은 모델과 제품 내선을로드 할 때
just tries to match the key-value pairs of names and waits between the cafe
단지 이름의 키 - 값 쌍을 일치 시키려고하고 카페 사이 대기
model and the product ext
모델 제품 EXT
so if the names of the same then your new network gets initialized from the
그래서 같은 이름은 다음 새로운 네트워크는에서 초기화되는 경우
values and the proto txt which is really really useful and convenient for fine
가치와 정말 정말 유용하고 좋은 편리하다 프로토 TXT
tuning but if the layers if the names don't match than those layers actually
조정하지만, 층 이름은 실제로 해당 계층보다 일치하지 않으면하면
initialize from scratch so this is how for example you can read nationalize the
이 예를 들어 당신이 국유화 읽을 수있는 방법 그래서 처음부터 초기화
output in cafe so to be a little bit more concrete if you've
당신이했습니다 경우 카페에서 출력 그래서 조금 더 구체적으로
maybe download an image that model then this larry is going on this final fully
아마 모델은 다음이 래리가 완전히 마지막에가는 이미지를 다운로드
connected layer that's output in class course will have a thousand outputs but
출력 클래스 과정에서의 연결 층은 천 출력이되지만
now maybe for some problem you care about you only want have 10 outputs
지금 어쩌면 당신은 당신에 대해 걱정 몇 가지 문제에 대한 10 출력을 원하는
you're gonna need to reindustrialize that final layer and realized it
당신은 마지막 층을 reindustrialize하는 거 필요가있어, 그것을 실현
randomly and fine-tune the network so the way that you do that is you need to
무작위로 미세 조정 네트워크는 그래​​서 당신이 할 방법은 당신이 필요하다
change the name of the lair in the Pro txt file to make sure that it's actually
실제로입니다 있는지 확인하기 위해 프로 txt 파일에있는 은신처의 이름을 변경
initialize randomly and not reading from the from from the cafe model and if you
무작위가 아닌 카페 모델과 경우에서 읽는 초기화
forget to do this then it'll actually crash and it'll give you a weird error
다음은 실제로 충돌합니다이 작업을 수행하는 것을 잊지 그것은 당신에게 이상한 오류를 줄 것이다
message about the shapes not aligning cause it'll be trying to store this
모양이이를 저장하려고 할 것이다 원인 정렬하지에 대한 메시지
thousand dimensional weight matrix into this ten dimensional thing from your new
새에서이 열 차원 일에 천 차원의 가중치 행렬
file and it won't work so the next step when working with cafe is to define the
파일 및 카페로 작업하는을 정의 할 때 그렇게 다음 단계를 작동하지 않습니다
solver the solver is also just a pro txt file you can see all the options for it
해석 솔버는 당신이 그것을위한 모든 옵션을 볼 수 있습니다 그냥 프로 txt 파일입니다
in that giant profile that I gave a link to a little look something like this for
나는이 같은 작은 모양의 무언가에 대한 링크를 준 거 프로필
Alex night maybe so that will define your learning rate and you're learning
알렉스 밤 그 학습 속도를 정의 할 것이다 당신은 배우고 어쩌면 있도록
way to K and your regularization how often to check everything like that but
방법은 k로하고 정규화가 얼마나 자주 그런 모든 것을 확인하지만,
these end up being less much less complex than that he's pro txt for the
이러한 덜 훨씬 덜 복잡 그는위한 프로 TXT 있다는보다 끝나게
networks this Alex neckties just maybe fourteen lines although what you will
네트워크이 알렉스 넥타이 다만 어쩌면 십사 라인 당신이되지만
see some times in practice is that if people want to have sort of complex
실제로 몇 번을 참조 것은 그 사람들은 복잡한의 종류가하려는 경우
trading pipelines where they first one I trained with 11 learning rate in certain
거래 파이프 라인 위치를 특정의 속도를 학습 나는 11 훈련 그들이 첫 번째
parts of the network they want to train with another learning rate certain parts
네트워크의 일부는 다른 학습 속도 특정 부분과 함께 훈련 할
of the network that you might end up with a cascade of different solver files
서로 다른 해석 파일의 폭포로 끝날 수있는 네트워크의
and actually run the most independent me we are sort of fine-tuning your own
실제로 우리가 일종의 자신을 미세 조정하는 가장 독립적 인 저를 실행
model in separate stages using different solvers so once you've done all that
다른 솔버를 사용하여 별도의 단계에서 모델은 모든 일을 한 번, 그래서 그
then you just trainer model so if you if you followed my advice and just use a
다음은 단지 트레이너 모델 내 조언을 따라하면 당신이 단지를 사용하는 경우 있도록
MTB and all these things about you just call this binary that is it that exists
MTB 당신은 그냥 존재, 즉 바이너리 전화에 대한 모든 것을
in campaign already so here you just passed your solver and your txt and
아직 여기 캠페인에 그냥 통과하여 해석하고 TXT 및
Europe retrain weights file if you're fine tuning and it'll run maybe Friday
유럽​​은 미세 조정 인 경우 무게가 파일을 재교육과 금요일 아마 실행합니다
maybe for a long time and just checking and savings to desk and you'll be happy
아마 오랜 시간 동안 그냥 확인하고 책상을 절감하고 알 수있을 것
one thing to point out here is that you specify which GPU it runs on this is
여기에서 지적하는 한 것은이가에 실행 GPU를 지정할 것입니다
your last text but you can actually run in CPR
마지막 텍스트하지만 당신은 실제로 CPR에서 실행할 수 있습니다
by setting this flag to my negative one and actually recent sometime in the last
마지막에 언젠가 내 음 하나에이 플래그를 설정하고 실제로 최근에 의해
year cafe added data parallelism to let you split up many batches across
올해 카페는 걸쳐 많은 배치를 분할 할 수있는 데이터 병렬 처리를 추가
multiple GPUs in your system you can actually add multiple GPUs on this flag
시스템에서 여러 GPU는 실제로이 플래그에 여러 개의 GPU를 추가 할 수 있습니다
and if you just say all been Cafe will automatically split up many batches
그냥 모든되어 카페를 말하면 자동으로 여러 배치를 분할합니다
across all the GPUs on your machine so that's really cool you've done multi GPU
컴퓨터에있는 모든 GPU를 통해이 정말 당신은 멀티 GPU를 수행 한 멋진 있도록
training without writing a single line of code pretty cool cafe oh yeah
오 코드 정말 멋진 카페의 한 줄을 작성하지 않고 훈련 그래
yeah I think so the question is how would you go about doing some more
그래, 정말 문제는 당신이 좀 더 일에 대해 이동하는 방법을 생각
complex initialization strategy for you maybe want to initialize the weights
당신은 아마 무게를 초기화 할 복잡한 초기화 전략
from a preacher and model and use those same way as in multiple parts of your
설교자와 모델에서의 여러 부분과 그 같은 방법을 사용하여
network and then the answer is that you probably can't do that with a simple
네트워크는 대답은 당신이 아마 간단한으로 그렇게 할 수 없다는 것입니다
mechanism you can kind of money on the weights and Python and that's probably
당신이 무게와 파이썬에 돈의 종류 할 수있는 메커니즘 그것은 아마
how you go about doing it right so I think we've mentioned this before that
내가 우리가 전에 언급 한 것 같아 바로 그래서 그 일에 대해 가지 방법
cafe has this really great models you you can download lots of different types
카페는 서로 다른 종류의 많은 다운로드 할 수 있습니다이 정말 좋은 모델이있다
of preteen models on a mission at and other datasets so this this model is it
이 때문에의 임무에 초반 이었죠 모델과 다른 데이터 세트의이 모델은이다
was really top-notch you've got Alex natin BGG you've got residents up there
정말 최고의 당신이 알렉스 natin BGG을 가지고 있었다 당신은 거기 주민있어
already pretty much lots and lots of really good models are up there so
이미 꽤 많이 많이와 정말 좋은 모델을 많이 그래서 거기있다
that's that's a really really strong point about cafe that it's really easy
그는 그것이 정말 쉽습니다 카페에 대한 정말 정말 장점입니다입니다
to download someone else's model and run it on your data are pointing to your
누군가 다른 사람의 모델을 다운로드를 가리키는 데이터에서 실행하는 방법
data
데이터
Cafe has a pipeline interface like I mentioned I
내가 언급 한 것처럼 카페는 파이프 라인 인터페이스를 가지고
since there are so many things to cover I don't think I can dive into detail
나는 세부 사항으로 뛰어들 수 있다고 생각하지 않습니다 충당하기 위해 너무 많은 일이 있기 때문에
here but as a kind of par for the course and cafe there's not really really great
여기에 있지만 코스와 카페 파의 일종으로 정말 정말 좋은이 아니다
documentation about the Python interface so you need to read the code and the
코드를 읽을 필요하고, 그래서 파이썬 인터페이스에 대한 설명서
whole
모든
the Python interface Street Cafe is mostly defined in these two in these two
파이썬 인터페이스 스트리트 카페는 대부분이 두에 두에 정의되어 있습니다
files this CPP file uses boost Python if you've ever used that before talks to
파일이 CPP 파일은 적에게 이야기하기 전에 것을 사용한 경우 파이썬을 향상 사용
wrap up some of the C++ classes and expose them to take on and then in this
는 C ++ 클래스의 일부를 마무리하고이에에 다음 걸릴에 노출
. py file it actually attach additional methods and gives you more Python
. 평 실제로 추가 방법을 첨부하고 더 많은 파이썬를 제공 파일
interface so if you wanna know what kinds of methods and data types are
인터페이스 당신은 어떤 방법과 데이터 타입의 종류 알고 싶어요 그래서 만약
available in the cafe pipe interface your best bet is to just read 3 through
카페 파이프에서 사용할 수있는 것이 가장 좋은 인터페이스 단지를 통해 3을 읽는 것입니다
these two files and they're not too long so it's it's pretty easy to do
이 두 파일 그리고 그들은 너무 오래 그것은 할 매우 쉽게 그래서 아니에요
yes the Python interface in general is is pretty useful it lets you do maybe
'예 일반적으로 파이썬 인터페이스는 당신이 아마 수행 할 수 있습니다 꽤 유용
crazy weight initialization strategies if you need to do something more complex
미친 체중 초기화 전략은 당신이 뭔가 더 복잡한 작업을 수행해야하는 경우
than just copy from a chain model it also makes it really easy to just get a
단지 체인 모델 복사보다 그것은 또한 정말 쉽게 단지를 얻을 수 있습니다
network and then run it forward and backward on with numpy from numpy array
네트워크는 다음 NumPy와 배열 NumPy와 함께 앞으로 뒤로 실행
is so for example you can implement things like deep dream and class
그래서 예를 들어, 당신은 깊은 꿈과 클래스 등을 구현할 수있다
visualisations similar to that you did on the homework you can also do that
당신이 숙제에 당신도 그렇게 할 수 않았다 유사한 시각화
quite easily using the Python interface on cafe where you just need to take data
아주 쉽게 그냥 데이터를 취할 필요가 카페에 파이썬 인터페이스를 사용하여
and then run it forward and backward through different parts of the network
다음 네트워크의 다른 부분을 통해 순방향 및 역방향 실행
work the Python interface is also quite nice if if you just want to extract
파이썬 인터페이스도 아주 좋은 일을 그냥 추출 할 경우 경우
features like you have some data that you have some free trade model and you
당신 같은 기능을 사용하면 일부 자유 무역 모델이 일부 데이터를 가지고 있고
want to track features from some part of the network and then maybe save them to
네트워크의 일부에서 기능을 추적 할 다음 어쩌면에 저장
disk maybe 2005 file were some downstream processing that's quite easy
디스크가 아마 2005 파일은 아주 쉽게 약간의 다운 스트림 처리했다
to do with the Python interface you can also actually Cafe has a kind of a new
당신이 할 수있는 파이썬 인터페이스를 수행하는 것은 실제로 카페는 새의 종류가
feature where you can actually define layers entirely in Python but this is
실제로 파이썬에서 레이어를 완전히 정의 할 수 있지만이 기능
I've never done it myself but it's it seems cool it seems nice but the
내가 직접 해본 적이 있지만, 그것은 좋은 것 같지만 냉각 보인다 년대
downside is that those layers will be CPU on me so we talked about
단점은 그 층이 나 CPU가 될 것입니다 그래서 우리는 대한 이야기​​입니다
communication bottlenecks between the CPU and GPU that if you write letters in
당신이 편지를 쓰는 경우 CPU와 GPU 사이의 통신 병목
Python then every forward and backward pass you'll be anchoring overhead I'm
파이썬은 모든 전후 패스가 난 오버 헤드가 고정됩니다
not transfer although one nice place where pipes and wires could be useful as
파이프와 전선으로 도움이 될 수 있습니다 하나의 좋은 장소 있지만 전송하지
custom loss functions so that's maybe something that you could keep in mind so
사용자 정의 손실 함수 그건 당신이 마음에 그렇게 유지 수있는 일이 어쩌면 그래서
the quick overview of Catholic pros and cons that really from my point of view
가톨릭 장점과 단점의 빠른 개요이 정말 내 관점에서
if all you wanna do is kind of train a simple basic feedforward network
당신 싶어하는 모든 경우 종류의 간단한 기본 피드 포워드 네트워크를 훈련
especially for classification and kathy is really really easy to get things up
특히 분류 및 캐시는 물건을 얻을 정말 쉽습니다
and running you don't have to write any code yourself you just use all these are
당신을 실행하면 자신이 방금 이러한 모든 사용하는 코드를 작성할 필요가 없습니다
pre-built tools and it's quite easy to run it has a Python interface which is
도구를 사전이 내장 그것은 파이썬 인터페이스를 실행하는 것은 매우 쉽다
quite nice for using a little to work for a little bit more complex use cases
조금 사용하기위한 아주 좋은 조금 더 복잡한 사용 사례에 대해 작동합니다
but it can be cumbersome when things get really crazy when you have these really
당신이 정말로이있을 때 일이 정말 미친 얻을 때하지만 성가신 될 수 있습니다
big networks like president especially with repeated module patterns they can
특히 그들이 할 수있는 반복 모듈 패턴 회장 같은 큰 네트워크
be tedious and for things like like recurrent networks where you want to
당신이 원하는 위치 지루한와 같은 재발 네트워크와 같은 것들에 대한 수
share waits between different parts of the network can be kind of company kind
네트워크의 다른 부분 사이의 공유 기다립니다 종류 회사의 종류 일 수있다
of cumbersome in cafe it is possible but it's probably not the best thing to use
카페에서 성가신의 그것은 가능하지만 아마 사용할 수있는 가장 좋은 것은 아니다
for that and the other downside the other big downside from my point of view
내 관점에서 다른 큰 단점이 및 다른 단점
is that when you want to find your own type of lair in cafe you end up having
당신이 카페에서 은신처의 자신의 유형을 찾을 때 갖는 끝날 것입니다
to write C++ code so that's not doesn't give you a very quick development cycle
그것이 당신에게 매우 빠른 개발주기를 제공하지 않습니다하지 그래서 C ++ 코드를 작성하는
so it's kind of a lot of kind of painful to write you letters so that's that's
그래서 그 그건 그래서 고통의 종류의 많은 종류의 당신에게 편지를 쓰고 있어요
why our world whirlwind tour of cafe so if there's any quick questions
우리의 세계는 카페의 여행을하는 간단한 질문이 있다면, 그래서 선풍 이유
yeah
네
cross validation and cafe so in the train Valparaiso txt you can try to find
교차 검증 및 카페 찾을 시도 할 수 있습니다이 txt 기차 발파라이소에서 매우
a training phase and a testing phase so generally alright like a train about
교육 단계와 테스트 단계는 그래서 일반적으로 약 기차처럼 좋아
product ext
제품 내선
and apply product ext and deploy will be used at on the task at hand but test
제품 내선을 적용하고 손하지만 테스트에서 작업에에서 사용되는 배포
phase of the trail product ext will be used for validation ok that's that's all
흔적 제품 내선의 위상은 그게 다야의 유효성 확인에 사용됩니다
there is to know about cabinet so the next one is torch so torch is really my
다음 하나는 토치 그래서 토치 정말 내 그래서 캐비닛에 대해 알고있다
personal favorite so I have a little bit of bias here just to get that out in the
내가 여기 편견 조금 그래서 개인적으로 좋아 단지에 그를 얻을 수
open that I've pretty much been using torch almost exclusively on my own
오픈 나는 꽤 많이 내 자신에 거의 독점적으로 토치를 사용했던 것을
projects in the last year or so so a torch is originally from NYU it's
작년에 정도 횃불 그래서 프로젝트는 것 NYU 출신
written in C and in lieu up and it's used a lot at Facebook indeed mind
C에서 최대 대신에 기록하고 페이스 북 참으로 마음에 많이 사용되는
especially I think also a lot of folks at Twitter use torch so one of the big
특히 나는 큰 중 하나 있도록 토치를 사용하는 트위터에서도 사람들을 많이 생각
things that freaks people out of course is that you have to write in lieu of
과정에서 사람들을 괴물 일들이 당신이 대신 작성해야한다는 것입니다
which I had never had never heard of or used before starting to work with torch
나는 듣지 또는 토치 작업을 시작하기 전에 사용 된 적이 적이있는
but it actually isn't too bad that lure is best highly this high-level scripting
하지만 실제로 유혹 가장 높은이 높은 수준의 스크립트는 것을 너무 나쁘지 않다
language that is really intended for embedded devices so it can run more
더 실행할 수 있도록 정말 임베디드 디바이스를위한 것입니다 언어
efficiently and it's a lot of very similar to JavaScript in a lot of ways
효율적으로는 많은 방법에서 자바 스크립트와 매우 유사 많이있어
so another cool thing about lou is that because it's meant to be run on embedded
그래서 루에 대한 또 다른 좋은 점은 그것이 의미가 있기 때문에 내장에서 실행할 수 있다는 것입니다
devices that you can actually do for loops are really fast and torch you know
당신이 실제로 루프를 위해 할 수있는 장치는 정말 빨리하고 성화 당신은 알고있다
how in Python if you're in a for loop it's going to be really slow that's
당신은 진짜로 그건 천천히 것 for 루프에서 어떻게 파이썬에서라면
actually totally fine to do in in torch because it actually uses just-in-time
실제로 적시를 사용하기 때문에 성화에의 할 사실은 완전히 잘
compilation to make these things really fast and torch is our newest most
이러한 일들이 정말 빨리 만들 수 컴파일과 성화는 우리의 최신 가장입니다
important JavaScript in that it is functional language functions are
이 기능 언어 기능이 인 것을 중요 자바 스크립트
first-class citizens it's very common to pass pass callbacks around to different
그것은 다른에 주위에 콜백을 통과 전달하는 매우 흔한 일류 시민
parts of your code you also is has this idea of protocol inheritance where
코드의 일부는 또한 프로토콜 상속 곳의이 아이디어를 가지고있다
they're sort of one data structure which in Lua is a table which you can think of
그들은 당신이 생각할 수있는 테이블 루아에있는 일종의 하나의 데이터 구조의 것
is being very similar to an object in javascript and you can implement things
당신이 일을 구현할 수있는 자바 스크립트 객체와 매우 유사되고있는
like object oriented programming using prototypical inheritance in a similar
객체 지향 프로그래밍 같은 비슷한에 프로토 타입 상속을 사용하여
way as you would in javascript and one of the town's one of the downsides
방법이 자바 스크립트에서와 그리고 도시의 하나 단점 중의 하나로서
actually the standard library
실제로 표준 라이브러리
is kind of annoying sometimes and things like handling strings and whatnot can be
취급 문자열과 이것 저것 할 수있다처럼 때로는 성가신 종류의 물건입니다
kind of cumbersome and maybe most annoying is its one indexed so all of
아마 가장 성가신 가시고의 종류는 그렇게 모든 인덱스의 하나입니다
your intuition about four loops will be a little bit off for a while but other
네 루프에 대한 당신의 직관은 한 동안 있지만 다른에 대해 조금 꺼집니다
than that it's pretty easy to pick up and I gave a link here to this website
보다가 데리러 아주 쉽게 그리고 나는이 웹 사이트에 여기에 링크를 준
claiming that you can learn Lua in 15 minutes it might be a little bit of an
당신이 15 분 루아를 배울 수 있다고 주장하는 것은 그것은 약간있을 수 있습니다
over so they might be overselling it a little bit but I think it is pretty easy
그들은 그것을 조금 지나치게 될 수 있으므로 이상하지만 난 그것을 아주 쉽게 생각
to pick up and start writing code and it pretty fast so the main idea behind
그래서 주요 아이디어 뒤에 꽤 빨리 그것을 선택하고 코드를 작성 시작하기
torch is this tensor class so you guys have been working in numpy a lot on your
토치 그래서 너희들에 NumPy와 많이 작업 된이 텐서 클래스 당신의
assignments and the way the assignments are kind of structured is that the numpy
할당 및 할당 종류의 구조화하는 방법은 NumPy와 것입니다
array gives you this really easy way to manipulate data in whatever way you want
배열은 당신에게 어떤 방법으로 당신이 원하는 데이터를 조작하는이 정말 쉬운 방법을 제공합니다
and then you can use that number higher rates of buildup other abstractions like
다음과 같은 축적 다른 추상화의 수 높은 비율을 사용할 수 있습니다
known that libraries and whatnot but really the numpy array just lets you
라이브러리와 이것 저것하지만 정말 NumPy와 배열이 당신을 할 것으로 알려져
manipulate data numerically in whatever way you want in complete flexibility so
당신이 그렇게 완벽한 유연성에 원하는 방식으로 숫자 데이터를 조작
if you are a call then maybe here's a look here's an example of some numpy
통화하는 경우 어쩌면 여기 봐 여기에 일부 NumPy와의 예
code that should be very familiar by now we're just computing a simple for a pass
지금 우리가 그냥 패스에 대한 간단한을 계산하고 의해 아주 잘 알고 있어야 코드
of cool air rail network so maybe black wasn't the best choice here but we're
냉기 철도 네트워크의 어쩌면 블랙은 여기 최선의 선택은 아니었지만 우리는있어
we're we're doing we're competing some some constants were competing some
우리는 우리는 우리가 어떤 어떤 상수 일부 경쟁하고 경쟁하는 일을하고있어
weights are getting some random data and we're doing a matrix multiply a rally in
가중치는 어떤 임의의 데이터를 얻고있다 그리고 우리는 매트릭스에서 집회를 곱하고있는
another major multiplied so that's that's very easy to write an umpire and
곱 또 다른 주요 그래서 그 그 심판을 작성하는 것은 매우 간단이고
actually this has almost a 120 translation into torched answers so now
실제로이 이제 불을 지른 답변에 거의 120 번역이
on the right this is the exact same code but using torched answers and so here
오른쪽이 동일한 코드를하지만, 그래서 여기에 불을 지른 답변을 사용하고
we're defining our backsides input size and all that we're defining our weights
우리의 가중치를 우리는 우리의 뒷부분 입력 크기를 정의하고 모든 우리는 정의하고 그
which are just torched answers were getting a random input vector we're
이는 단지 불을 지른 대답은 우리가있어 임의의 입력 벡터를 얻고 있었다있다
doing a forward pass this is doing a matrix multiply up to our sponsors this
이 행렬을하고있다 전진 패스를하고 우리의 스폰서까지 번식이
c-max
C-최대
element wise maximum that's a real issue and then we can compute cores using
진짜 문제이고 우리가 사용하는 코어를 계산할 수 요소 현명한 최대
another matrix multiply so in general pretty much any kind of code used
코드의 일반적인 거의 모든 종류의 사용에 있도록 다른 행렬 곱셈
trading an umpire is pretty easy
심판을 거래하는 것은 매우 간단합니다
pretty much has almost a one-by-one line-by-line translation into using
꽤 많이 사용에 거의 하나씩 라인 별 번역이
torched answers instead
불을 지른 대답 대신
so also remember in umpire that it's really easy to swap and use different
그래서 또한 교환 및 다른 사용하기 정말 쉬운 것이 심판의 기억
data types we talked about this ad nauseam the last lecture but at least in
우리는이 광고에 대해 얘기 데이터 유형은 최소한의 마지막 강의를 싫증하지만,
numpy to switch to maybe a 32 bit floating point all you need to do is
당신이 할 필요가 아마 32 비트 부동 소수점로 전환 할 NumPy와
cast your data to this other data type and it turns out that that's very very
이 다른 데이터 유형으로 데이터를 캐스팅하고는 아주 아주 있다고 밝혀
easy to do in torture as well that our data type is now this this strength and
뿐만 아니라 우리의 데이터 유형이이 강도가 지금 있음을 고문 할 쉽게
then we can easily cast our data to another data type but here's where two
우리는 쉽게 다른 데이터 유형으로 우리의 데이터를 전송할 수 있지만, 여기 어디이있어
years though so this next slide as the real reason why torture is infinitely
년 그래서 진짜 이유 등이 다음 슬라이드 고문은 무한 이유하지만
better than numpy and that's that the GPU is just another data type so when
NumPy와보다 나은 즉 GPU는 또 다른 데이터가 그렇게 할 때 입력 한 것을이다
you are right when you wanna run code on the GPU in torch you use this you import
당신이 횃불의 GPU에서 코드를 실행할 싶어 할 때 당신은 당신이 가져 이것을 사용 옳다
another package and you have another time another data type which is torched
다른 패키지와 다른 시간을 지른 또 다른 데이터 형식이
a tensor and now you cast your tensors to this other data type and now they
텐서와 지금이 다른 데이터 유형에 텐서를 캐스팅하고 지금은
live on the GPU and running any kind of numerical operations on the tensors just
GPU에서 살고 텐서에 수치 연산의 종류를 실행 단지
runs on the GPU so it's really really easy and torch to just write generic
정말 정말 간단하고 토치 그냥 일반 쓸 수 있도록 GPU에서 실행
tenser scientific computing code to run I GPU and be really fast so this like I
tenser 과학 컴퓨팅 코드는 I GPU를 실행하고 정말 빨리 그래서 이런 식으로 내가 할 수
said these tensors are really you should think of them as similar to numpy raised
이 텐서 정말 당신은 유사한 그들을 제기 NumPy와 생각해야되는 것을
and there's a lot of documentation on but different kinds of methods that you
및 방법의 종류 만에 문서의 많은 거기에 당신
can work within 10 service up here and get up this documentation isn't super
여기까지 10 서비스 내에서 작동하고이 문서를 얻을 수있는 것은 슈퍼 아니다
complete but it's it's not bad so you should take a look at it so the next but
완전한하지만 당신이 다음 있도록에서 살펴 보셔야합니다 있도록이 나쁘지 않아 야하지만,
in practice you end up not really using the tensors too much in torch instead
실제로 당신은 정말 대신 횃불에 너무 많이 텐서를 사용하지 결국
use this other package called an end for neural networks so and and is this
그래서 신경 네트워크의 끝이라는 다른 패키지를 사용하고 이것입니다
pretty thin wrapper that actually defines neural network package just in
실제로 그냥 신경 네트워크 패키지를 정의하는 매우 얇은 래퍼
terms of these tents in terms of these tents are objects you should think of
이 텐트의 관점에서이 텐트의 조건은 당신이 생각해야 개체
this as being like a BPR more industrial strength version of the homework code
이 숙제 코드의 BPR 더 산업용 강도 버전처럼 인 것으로
base where you have this this tenth this and the array this tensor abstraction
기본이이이 열 번째와 배열이 텐서 추상화가 어디
and then you implement an aromatic library on top of that in a nice clean
다음은 좋은 깨끗한에서 그 꼭대기에 방향족 라이브러리를 구현
interface so here's the same to larry Adler network using the N package so we
인터페이스는 그래서 여기에 우리를 N 패키지를 사용 래리 애들러 네트워크에 동일합니다
define our network has a sequential so it's gonna be a stack of of sequential
이 거 순차적의 스택 수 그래서 우리의 네트워크가 순차적가 정의
operations it's gonna we're gonna first have a linear which is a fully connected
작업을 우리가 완전히 연결되어 선형이 처음거야 거입니다
from our input mentioned marketing to mention we're gonna have a railing and
우리의 입력이 마케팅을 언급에서 우리는거야 난간을 가지고 언급
another lender now we can actually get the weights and gradients in second one
다른 대출은 지금 우리가 실제로 두 번째의 무게와 그라디언트를 얻을 수 있습니다
to answer for each using this get parameters method to now waits will be a
지금 대기가 될 것이 얻을 매개 변수 방법을 사용하여 각각에 대한 대답
single torched answer that will have all the way to the network and graduates
네트워크 및 졸업생 모든 방법이있을 것이다 단일 불을 지른 답변
will be a single torched answer for all of the above ingredients we can generate
우리가 생성 할 수 있습니다 위의 모든 재료에 대해 하나의 횃불 대답을 할 것이다
some random data now to a forward pass we just call Matt the format on the
어떤 임의의 데이터는 이제 앞으로 패스에 우리는 단지의 형식 매트를 호출
object using our data this gives us our scores to computer loss we have a
이 우리에게 컴퓨터 손실에 대한 우리의 점수 우리는이를 제공합니다 우리의 데이터를 사용하여 객체
separate criterion object that is our loss function so we computer lost by
그래서 우리는 컴퓨터에 의해 잃어버린 우리의 손실 함수입니다 별도의 기준 객체
calling the fourth method of the criteria now we've done our forecast
기준의 네 번째 메서드를 호출하면 지금 우리는 우리의 예측을 수행 한
easy and backward pass we first set and 20 call a backward on the loss function
우리가 처음 설정 쉽고 뒤로 패스 20 호출 손실 함수에 역
and then a backward I'm at work now this has updated all of the gradients for the
내가 지금 일에있어 다음 역이는의 그라데이션을 모두 업데이트했습니다
network in the grad params so we can just make a gradient stuff very easily
대학원에서 네트워크는 우리가 그냥 아주 쉽게 그라데이션 물건을 만들 수 있습니다 params는
so this would be multiplying the graduates by the opposite of learning
그래서 이것은 학습의 반대에 의해 졸업생을 곱한 것
rate and then adding it to the ways that's a simple gradient descent update
레이트하고 간단한 그래디언트 디센트 갱신의 방법에 추가
rights that's that's all of the rights that would have been maybe a little bit
그것은 어쩌면 조금했을 모든 권한을의 권리
more clear but we have not we have weights graduates who have lost function
더 명확하지만 우리는 우리가 기능을 잃은 무게 졸업생을하지 않은
we get random data from forward and backward make an update and as as you
우리는 앞으로에서 임의의 데이터를 얻을 뒤로 업데이 트를 확인하고 같이
might expect from looking at that answer it's quite easy to make this thing run
그 대답보고에서 기대할 수있는 것이이 일을 실행할 수 있도록하는 것은 매우 쉽다
on GPU so to run on these networks on the GPU we import a couple new packages
GPU에 우리가 몇 가지 새로운 패키지를 가져 GPU에서 이러한 네트워크에서 실행
through torture and to an end which are two versions of everything and then we
고문을 통해 모든 것을 두 가지 버전이 끝과 우리
just need to cast our network and our loss function to this other data type
그냥이 다른 데이터 유형으로 우리의 네트워크와 우리의 손실 함수를 캐스팅해야
and we also need to cast our data and labels and now this whole network will
우리는 또한 우리의 데이터와 레이블을 캐스팅 할 필요가 지금이 모든 네트워크는 것
run and trained on the GPU so it's it's pretty easy now in what was that like 40
그것은 그 40 어땠는지 지금 매우 쉽다는 그래서 실행하고 GPU에 대한 교육을
lines of code we've written a fully connected network and we can train on
코드 라인은 우리가 완전히 연결 네트워크를 작성했습니다 우리는에 훈련 할 수있다
the GPU but one problem here is that we're just using vanilla gradient
여기에 GPU하지만 하나의 문제는 우리가 그냥 바닐라 그라데이션을 사용하는 것입니다
descent which is not so great and as you saw on the assignments other things like
너무 큰되지 않고 하강 당신은 할당과 같은 다른 것들에 본대로
out on our mess popped into work much better in practice so to solve that
아웃 실제로는 훨씬 더 나은 작업에 불쑥 우리의 혼란에 이렇게 것을 해결하기 위해
torch gives us the opportunity package so optimist quite easy to use again we
성화는 우리에게 다시 사용하기 때문에 낙관적 아주 쉽게 기회 패키지를 제공합니다 우리
just import a new package up here
바로 여기에 새로운 패키지를 가져
here and now what changes is that we actually need to define this callback
여기 그리고 지금 무엇을 변경하는 것은 우리가 실제로이 콜백을 정의 할 필요가있다
function so before we were just calling forward and backward exclude explicitly
우리가 앞으로 전화 및 역방향 명시 적으로 제외되었다 전에 있도록 기능
ourself instead we're going to find this callback function that will run the
해결할 대신 우리는을 실행이 콜백 함수를 찾을거야
network forward and backward on data and then return the loss and the gradient
네트워크는 앞으로 데이터를 뒤로하고 손실과 기울기를 반환
and now to make an update stop on our network will actually pass this callback
지금 우리의 네트워크에 업데이트 정지 실제로이 콜백을 통과 할 수 있도록하는
function to this Adam method from the Optim package so this this is maybe a
Optim을 패키지에서이 아담 방법과 기능 때문에이이 어쩌면이다
little bit awkward but you know we can use any kind of update rule using just a
조금 어색하지만 당신은 우리가 단지를 사용하여 업데이트 규칙의 어떤 종류를 사용할 수 있습니다 알고
couple lines of change from what we had before and again this is very easy to
우리가 전에 한 어떤에서 변화의 몇 라인은 다시는 매우 간단합니다
add to run on the GPU by just casting everything to go right so as we saw in
단지 우리가 본 바로 위하여 가고 모든 캐스팅하여 GPU에서 실행에 추가
cafe cafe sort of implements everything in terms of next and layers and cafe has
카페 카페 일종의 다음의 용어와 레이어와 카페가 모든 것을 구현
this really hard distinction between that and the lair in torch they don't we
그 사이 정말 열심히 구분 및 토치의 은신처 그들은 우리는하지 않습니다
don't really draw this distinction everything is just a model so the entire
정말이 구별 모든 것을 그릴 수없는 것은 전체 그래서 그냥 모델입니다
network is a module and also each individual larry is a module so modules
네트워크 모듈이며, 또한 각각의 모듈 래리 그래서 모듈은
are just classes that are defined in lieu of that rut that are implemented
구현되는 틀에 박힌 생활 대신에 정의되어 단지 클래스는
using that answer API so these modules are since the written law they're quite
그 대답의 API를 사용하므로 이러한 모듈은 꽤있어 서면 법부터입니다
easy to understand so many here is the fully connected now is the the fully
여기에 많은 이해하기 쉬운 완전 이제 연결된 완전하다
connected larry and this is the constructor you can see it's just
래리 연결이 당신이 그냥 볼 수있는 생성자
setting up tents as for the weight and the bias and because this tensor API in
가중치 및 바이어스 용으로이 텐서 API로 인해 텐트 설정
torch lets us easily run the same code on GPU and CPU than all of these layers
성화는 우리가 쉽게 이러한 모든 층보다 GPU와 CPU에 동일한 코드를 실행할 수 있습니다
will just be written in terms of the tensor API and then Heasley run on both
단지 텐서 API의 관점에서 작성하고 Heasley 모두에서 실행됩니다
devices so these modules need to implement a forward and backward so far
장치이므로 이러한 모듈은 전후 원경 구현해야
forward babe decided to call it update output so here's the example of the
앞으로 아기 때문에 여기의 예제는 출력을 업데이트 부르기로 결정
update output for the full text of later there's actually a couple cases they
의 전체 텍스트에 대한 업데이트 출력은 나중에 실제로 몇 가지 경우가있어 그들이
need to deal with a couple different cases here to be with me back vs non me
다시 비 대 나와 함께 여기 몇 가지 경우를 처리해야하는 날
back in parts but other than that but should be quite easy to read before
다시 부분에 있지만, 다른 것보다 있지만, 사용하기 전에 반드시 숙지 아주 쉬워야한다
further backward pass there's a pair of methods update grad input which receives
더 뒤로받는 방법 업데이트 대학원 입력 한 쌍의 거기 통과
the upstream gradients and computes the gradients respected
상류 구배 및 계산하는 그라디언트 존중
input and again this is just implemented in the tensor API so it's very easy to
입력 및 다시 그냥 텐서 API로 구현됩니다 그래서 그것은 매우 쉽게
understand its just a bit just the same type of thing you saw on homework and we
일의 그 조금을 이해 그냥 같은 유형은 숙제 우리에보고
also implement and accumulate grab parameters which computes the gradients
또한 구현하고 기울기를 계산하는 잡아 매개 변수를 축적
with respect to the weights of the network as you saw in the constructor
네트워크의 무게에 대하여 당신은 생성자에서 본대로
the weights on the biases are held in instance variables this module and
편견의 무게가 인스턴스 변수이 모듈에서 개최되며,
accumulate grad parameters will receive gradients from upstream and accumulate
대학원 매개 변수는 업스트림에서 그라디언트를 받게됩니다 축적과 축적
gradients of the parameters with respect to the upstream radians and again this
다시 상류 라디안과 관련하여 파라미터 그라디언트
is very simple just using the tensor API
단지 텐서 API를 사용하여 매우 간단합니다
torch actually has a ton of different modules available the documentation here
토치 실제로 사용 가능한 다른 모듈의 톤 여기에 문서를 가지고
can be a little bit out of date but if you just go on get up you can see all
당신은 단지에 가면 날짜가 조금있을 수 있지만, 당신은 모든 확인할 수 있습니다 일어나서
the files that give you all the goodies to play with and he's actually get
파일은 당신에게 놀 수있는 모든 케이크를 제공하는 그는 실제로 얻을 수있어
updated a lot so just a point out a couple these these pre-war just added me
많은 그래서 그냥 포인트 아웃이이 전쟁 전 그냥 날 추가 몇 업데이트
last week so torches always adding new modules that you can add your networks
횃불은 항상 당신이 당신의 네트워크를 추가 할 수있는 새로운 모듈을 추가, 그래서 지난 주
which is pretty fun but when these existing modules aren't good enough it's
이는 꽤 재미 있지만, 이러한 기존의 모듈이 충분하지 않은 때이다
actually very easy to write your own so because you can just implement these
그냥이를 구현할 수 있기 때문에, 그래서 자신을 쓰기 실제로 매우 쉽게
things using these tenser using the tensor API and just implement the
텐서 API를 사용하여 단지를 구현하는이 tenser를 사용하는 것
forward and backward it's not much harder than implementing layers on the
전후 그것은에 구현 층보다 훨씬 더 어렵다
homeworks so here's just a small example this is a stupid module that just takes
그래서 여기에 숙제 단지 작은 예입니다 이것은 단지 걸리는 바보 모듈입니다
its input and multiply it by two and you can see we implement the update graph
입력과 2로 곱하면 우리가 업데이트 그래프를 구현 볼 수 있습니다
template and now we've implemented a new layer and torque just twenty lines of
템플릿과 지금 우리는 단지 스물 라인 새 레이어과 토크를 구현 한
code and then that's really easy and then it's very easy to use in other code
코드는 그 정말 쉽게 후 다른 코드를 사용하는 것은 매우 쉽다
just import it and I you can add its networks and so on and the really cool
그냥 가져 와서 나는 당신의 네트워크를 추가 등등과 정말 멋진 할 수 있습니다
thing about this is because this is just the tensor API you can do whatever kind
이것은 당신이 할 수있는 단지 텐서 API이기 때문에 이것에 대해 것은 무엇이든 종류
of arbitrary thing you want inside of these forward and backward if you need
임의의 일이 당신 앞으로 이러한 내부 원하고 필요한 경우 뒤로
to do for loops or complicated and parent of code or anything or maybe
아마 코드 또는 아무것도 또는 루프 또는 복잡하고 부모를 위해해야​​ 할 일
stochastic things for drop out or rationalization than any kind of any
어떤 어떤 종류의보다 밖으로 드롭 또는 합리화 확률 일
whatever kind of code you want to look forward and backward pass you just
당신은 기대 할 뒤로 당신을 통과 코드의 어떤 종류
implemented yourself inside these modules so it's usually very easy very
그것은 일반적으로 매우 간단 매우 그래서 이러한 모듈 내부에 직접 구현
easy to implement your own new types of players and torch so torch but of course
토치 있도록하지만, 물론 선수들과 토치의 자신의 새로운 유형을 쉽게 구현할 수
using individual layers on their own isn't so useful
자신의 개별 레이어를 사용하는 것은 매우 유용하지 않습니다
we need people to stitch them together into larger networks
우리는 더 큰 네트워크로 함께 스티치 할 사람이 필요
so far this torch uses containers we already saw one in the previous example
지금까지이 성화는 우리가 이미 앞의 예에서 일을보고 용기를 사용
which was this sequential container so consequential container is just a stack
이는이 순차적 컨테이너 그래서 결과적 컨테이너 그냥 스택이다
of modules that all we're one who receives the output from the previous
모든 우리는 이전의 출력을 수신하여 하나있어 모듈
one and just go back that's probably the most commonly used another one you might
하나는 그냥 가서 그게 아마 당신이 수도 가장 일반적으로 사용되는 또 다른 하나
see is this parent is this cunt at table so maybe if you have an input and you
볼이 입력이 있고 경우이 부모가 어쩌면 테이블이 성기입니다
want to apply different to different modules to the same input than the
댄 동일한 입력에 다른 모듈에 다른 적용 할
content table as you do that and you receive the output Celeste another one
콘텐츠 테이블 당신은 그렇게 당신은 다른 출력 셀레스트를받는
you might see as a parallel table if you have a list of inputs and you want to
당신이 입력의 목록이있는 경우는 병렬 테이블로 볼 수 있습니다 당신이 원하는
apply different modules to different each element of the list then you can
다음 다른에리스트의 각 요소를 다른 모듈을 수행 할 수 있습니다 적용
use a parallel tabor table for that sort of the construction but when things get
상황이 오면 건설의 종류에 대한 병렬 타 보르 테이블을 사용하지만,
really complicated so actually those those containers that I just told you
정말 그렇게 실제로 내가 당신에게하는 그 용기를 복잡
should in theory be easy to be possible to implement just about aids apology you
이론적으로 쉽게해야하는 보조 당신을 사과 단지에 대해 구현하는 것이 가능합니다
want but it can be really hairy in practice to wire up really complicated
원하는하지만 정말 복잡 묶는 연습에 정말 털이 수 있습니다
things using those containers so torch provides another package called pennant
토치 페넌트라는 다른 패키지를 제공하므로 그 용기를 사용하는 것
graph that lets you hook up
당신이 훅 수 있습니다 그래프
container hook up things more complicated topologies pretty easily so
컨테이너 훅 가지 더 복잡한 토폴로지 아주 쉽게 그렇게
here's an example if we have maybe if we have three inputs we want to produce one
우리가있는 경우 여기에 우리가 3 개의 입력이있는 경우 어쩌면 우리가 하나를 생성 할 예입니다
outputs and we want to produce them with this pretty simple update rule that
출력과 우리는 아주 간단 업데이트 규칙을 생성하려는
corresponds to this type of computational graph that we've seen many
우리는 많은 봤어요 계산 그래프의이 유형에 해당
times in lecture for different types of problems so you could actually implement
당신이 실제로 구현할 수 있도록 문제의 다른 유형에 대한 강의에서 배
this just fine using parallel and sequential and cunt at table but it
이 단지 사용하여 고급 병렬 및 순차 및 테이블 성기하지만 그것을
could be kind of a mass so when you wanna do things like this it's very
당신 싶어이 같은 일을 할 때 그래서 아주의 질량의 종류 수
common to send a graph instead so this graph code is is quite easy so here this
이 그래프 코드가 대신 있도록 그래프를 전송하는 것이 일반적 그래서 여기이 매우 쉽습니다
function is going to build a module using a graph and then return it so here
함수는 그래프를 사용하여 모듈을 구축하고 그래서 여기를 반환하는 것입니다
we import the graph package and then inside here this is a bit of money
우리는 그래프 패키지를 가져온 다음 여기 안에이 돈의 비트입니다
syntax so this is actually not a tensor this is the finding a symbolic variable
구문은 그래서 이것은 실제로는이 상징적 인 변수를 발견하는 텐서 아니다
so this is saying that our our tents or object is going to receive XY and Z as
그래서 이것은 우리의 우리 텐트 또는 객체로 XY 및 Z를 받으려고하는 것을 말하고있다
inputs and now share were actually doing symbolic operations on those inputs so
입력과 현재 점유율은 실제로 그렇게 그 입력에 상징적 인 작업을하고 있었다
here we're saying that
여기에 우리가 말을하는지
we wanted to have a pointwise edition of X&Y we want to have played twice
우리는 우리가 두 번 연주 한 할 X & Y의 점별 버전을 가지고 싶어
multiplication of ANZ store that and be and now pointwise edition of A&B and
및 수 ANZ 저장소의 곱셈과 A & B의 지금 점별 판과
store that and see and again these are not actual tenser objects these are now
이러한 실제적인 tenser이 지금의 객체이다 다시 저장하고보고
sort of symbolic references that are you being used to build up this
당신이 구축하는 데 사용되는 기호 참조의 종류
computational graph in the background and now we can actually returned a
계산 백그라운드에서 그래프와 지금 우리가 실제로 반환 할 수 있습니다
module here where we say that our module will have input X Y and Z and outputs
우리는 우리의 모듈은 입력 XY 및 Z 출력을 것이라고 여기 모듈
see and this end I G module will actually give us an object conforming to
볼이 엔드 IG 모듈은 실제로 우리에 부합하는 객체를 제공합니다
the module API that implements its computation so then after we build the
그럼 우리가 구축 한 후 그 계산을 구현하는 모듈 API
Montreal we can construct concrete court torched answers and then feed them into
몬트리올 우리는 콘크리트 법원이 답변을 지른 구성 할 수 있습니다 다음에 그들을 먹여
the module that will actually compute the function so a torch actually quite
실제로 기능을 너무 횃불 사실은 꽤 계산됩니다 모듈
good at preteen models there is a package called load campaign that lets
초반 이었죠 모델을 잘 할 수있는 패키지라는로드 캠페인이있다
you load up many different types of pre-trial models from cafe and it'll
당신은 카페에서 사전 시험 모델의 많은 다른 유형을로드하고는거야
convert them into their torture equivalents you can load up the cafe
그들의 고문의 등가물로 변환 당신은 카페를로드 할 수 있습니다
product ext and the cafe model file and it'll turn into a giant stack of
제품 내선 및 카페 모델 파일과는의 거대한 스택에 설정합니다
sequential mayors load Cafe is not super General Beau and only works for certain
연속 시장은, 카페 슈퍼 일반 보하지로드하고 특정 작동
types of networks but in particular load Cafe will let you load up Alex not and
네트워크 그러나 특정 부하 카페의 종류는 알렉스를하지로드 할 것이며,
campaign and PGG so they're probably some of the most commonly used there are
그들은 아마 가장 일반적으로 몇 가지있어 수 있도록 캠페인 및 PGG이 있습니다 사용
also a couple different implementations you load up Google Matt into into torch
또한 몇 가지 다른 구현 당신은 횃불로 구글 매트에로드
to let you load up retrain Google that models into torch and actually very
당신이 재시도 구글을로드 할 수 있도록 그 모델 성화에 실제로 매우
recently Facebook went ahead and reimplemented the residual networks
최근 페이스 북은 잔류 네트워크를 나서서 다시 구현
straight up in torch and they released preteen models for that so between Alex
바로 횃불 최대 알렉스 사이 때문에 그들은 그것을 위해 초반 이었죠 모델 출시
not campaign at BG Group and ResNet I think that's probably everything you
BG 그룹과 ResNet에서 캠페인되지 그게 아마 모든 것을 당신을 생각
need all the preteen models that most people want to use another point is that
이다 대부분의 사람들이 다른 점을 이용하려는 모든 초반 이었죠 모델 필요
because torches using lure we can't use pip to install packages and there's
횃불이 미끼를 사용하기 때문에 우리는 패키지를 설치 핍 사용하고있을 수 없습니다
another very similar idea called barracks that's easily install new
쉽게 새로운 설치할 것 막사라는 또 다른 매우 유사한 아이디어
packages an update packages
업데이트 패키지를 패키지
that's quite very easy to use
그것은 아주 사용하기 매우 쉽습니다
and this is kind of just a list of some packages that I find very useful in
이 종류의 나는 매우 유용한 몇 가지 패키지 단지 목록입니다
torch so there could be undone by names you can read and write to HDR 5 files
이름으로이 취소 할 수 있도록 성화는 5 파일을 읽고 HDR 쓸 수 있습니다
you can read and write JSON there's this funny one from Twitter autorad that is a
당신은 인 트위터 autorad에서이 재미 하나가 거기에 읽기 및 JSON을 쓸 수 있습니다
little bit like the animal which will talk about it a bit but I haven't used
조금하지만 사용하지 않은 얘기 할 동물처럼 조금
it but it's kind of cool to look at and actually Facebook has a pretty useful
하지만 가지를보고 멋진 실제로 페이스 북은 꽤 유용이
library for torches while that implements a fifty convolutions and also
횃불에 대한 라이브러리는 또한 오십 회선과를 구현하면서
implements data-parallel and model parallelism
데이터 병렬 모델 병렬 처리를 구현
so that's pretty a pretty nice thing to have so very typical workflow in torch
그래서 그 횃불에 이렇게 아주 일반적인 워크 플로우가 꽤 꽤 좋은 일이
is that you'll have some preprocessing script often and pecan that'll
당신이 있습니다 종종 몇 가지 전처리 스크립트를 가지고 그 피칸 것이다
preprocess your data and dump it on to some nice format in desk usually HDL 5
전처리 데이터와는 일반적으로 책상 HDL 5에 몇 가지 좋은 형식으로 그것을 덤프
for big things and Jason little things then you will I'll typically write a
큰 일 제이슨 작은 것들에 대해 당신은 내가 일반적으로 쓰기 것이다 것
trained at low up at all read from the HDL 5 and train the model and optimize
최대 낮은에서 훈련에있는 모든 HDL 5에서 읽고 모델을 학습하고 최적화
the model and save checkpoints the desk and then usually I have some evaluate
모델과는 체크 포인트에게 책상을 저장하고 일반적으로 좀 평가가
script that loads up a train model and does it for something useful so a case
기차 모델을로드하고 그래서 뭔가 유용한 경우 그것을하지 스크립트
study for this type of workflow is this project I put up on github a week ago
워크 플로우의이 유형에 대한 연구는 내가 일주일 전에 GitHub의에 올려이 프로젝트
that implements character level language models and torch so here there's a
즉 문자 수준의 언어 모델과 토치 그래서 여기에 거기를 구현
preprocessing script that converts text files into HTML 5 files there's a
HTML 5에 텍스트 파일을 변환 전처리 스크립트는 거기에 파일을
training script that loads for html5 and trains these recurrent networks and then
HTML5에 대한로드하고이 재발 네트워크와 열차 훈련 스크립트
there's a sampling script that loads up the checkpoints generate tax so that's
그건 있도록 검사 점은 세금이 생성 최대로드 샘플링 스크립트가있다
that's kind of like my typical workflow and torch so the quick pros and cons I
즉, 빠른 장점과 단점 나는 나의 일반적인 워크 플로우 및 토치와 같은 종류의
would say about torture that its lure is a big turnoff for people but I don't
그 유혹은 사람들을위한 큰 분기점하지만 나는하지 않는 것이 고문에 대해 말할 것입니다
think it's actually that big a deal it's definitely less plug and play in cafe so
큰 거래는 확실히 덜 플러그가 있다고 실제로 생각하고 그래서 카페에서 재생
you'll end up writing a lot of your own code typically which maybe is a little
당신은 아마 조금 전형적으로 자신의 코드를 많이 작성하게 될 겁니다
bit more overhead but also gives you more flexibility it has a lot of modular
또한 더 많은 오버 헤드하지만 비트는 당신이 모듈을 많이 가지고 더 많은 유연성을 제공
pieces that are easy to plug and play and the like the standard library
플러그 앤 플레이하기 쉽고 조각 표준 라이브러리처럼
because it's all written in blue it's quite easy to read and quite easy to
이 모든 푸른로 작성하기 때문에 읽기가 매우 간단하고 아주 쉽게
understand there's a lot of preteen models which is quite nice but
아주 좋은 초반 이었죠 모델이 많이있어 이해하지만,
unfortunately it's it's a little bit awkward to use for recurrent networks in
불행하게도 그것의 재발 네트워크를 사용하는 것이 조금 어색입니다
general so when you wanna have one month when you want to have multiple modules
일반 그래서 당신은 당신이 여러 개의 모듈을하고자 할 때 한 달 가지고 싶어 할 때
that share weights with each other you can actually do this and torch but it's
서로 공유하는 가중치는 실제로이와 횃불을 할 수 있지만입니다
it's kind
그것은 종류의
brittle and you can run into subtle bugs there so that's that's probably the
취성 그 아마의 그, 그래서 당신은 거기에 미묘한 버그로 실행할 수 있습니다
biggest caveat is that recurrent networks can be tricky
가장주의해야 할 점은 재발 네트워크가 까다로운 일이 될 수 있다는 것입니다
any any questions about torch yeah yeah yeah but it's not out of the question
어떤 어떤 토치에 대한 질문이 그래 그래하지만 질문에서이 아니다
was about how how bad are four loops and pecan is interpreted right so that's
그, 그래서 네 루프와 피칸를 잘 해석하는 방법 나쁜 방법에 대해이었다
that's really why for these are really bad in Python because it's interpreted
즉, 해석 있기 때문에이 파이썬에서 정말 나쁜 이유에 대해 정말
and every for lupus actually doing quite a lot of memory allocation and other
실제로 메모리 할당과 다른 꽤 많은 일 루푸스에 대한 모든
things behind the scenes but if you've ever use JavaScript then loops and
무대 뒤에서 일하지만 만약 당신이 자바 스크립트를 사용 한 경우 다음 루프와
JavaScript tend to be pretty fast because the runtime actually just
자바 스크립트는 꽤 빨리하는 경향이 있기 때문에 런타임 실제로 단지
compile the code on the fly down to native code so loops in JavaScript are
자바 스크립트에서 루프 그래서 네이티브 코드까지 즉석에서 코드를 컴파일
really fast and fluid and lou actually has a similar mechanism where it'll sort
정말 빠르고 유체 및 루 실제로 어디 정렬거야 유사한 메커니즘을 가지고
of automatically and magically compiled code for human genetic code so your lips
인간의 유전자 코드의 자동 마술 컴파일 된 코드 입술 때문에
can be really fast but that only I'm writing custom vectorized code still can
정말 빨리하지만 난 여전히 사용자 지정 벡터화 코드를 쓰고 있다고 할 수 있습니다
give you a lot of speed up all rights we've got now maybe half an hour left to
우리가 가진 모든 권한을 당신에게 속도 업을 많이주고 지금 아마 반 시간은 왼쪽
cover two more frameworks so we're running out of time so next up is no
아니 우리가 그래서 옆에 시간이 부족하고, 그래서 두 개 더 프레임 워크를 커버
such thing I know is from Joshua banjos group at the University of Montreal and
내가 아는 같은 건 몬트리올 대학에서 여호수아 밴조 그룹에서이며,
it's really all about computational graphs so we saw a little bit innn graph
우리는 그래프 innn 조금을 보았다 그래서 계산 그래프에 대해 정말 전부
from torch that computation crafts are this pretty nice way to stitch together
토치에서 그 계산 공예 함께 스티치이 꽤 좋은 방법입니다
big complicated architectures and Fionna really takes this idea of computation on
큰 복잡한 아키텍처와 Fionna 정말 계산이 아이디어에 소요
graphics and runs with it to the extreme and it also has some high-level library
그래픽 및 실행 그것 극단적하고 또한 약간 높은 수준의 라이브러리를 갖는다
is scarce and lasagna that will touch on as well so here's the same computation
여기에 같은 계산이 그래서 부족뿐만 아니라에 터치합니다 라자냐입니다
craft we saw in the context of a graph before and we can actually walk through
우리가 전에 그래프의 맥락에서 본 공예 우리는 실제로 통해 걸을 수
implementation of this in 2010 so you can see that in here we're importing
2010 년이의 구현은 그래서 당신은 여기에 우리가 가져 오는 것을 볼 수 있습니다
fiato and the fiato tenser object and now here we're defining XY and Z as
fiato과 fiato의 tenser 객체와 지금 여기에 우리가 같이 XY 및 Z를 정의하고
symbolic as symbolic variables this is actually very similar to the end and
이 실제로 말과 매우 유사 기호와 같은 기호 변수
graph example we saw just a few slides ago
그래프의 예를 우리는 불과 몇 슬라이드 전에 보았다
so that these are actually not numpy raise these are sort of symbolic objects
이 실제로되도록하는 것은 이러한 종류의 상징적 인 개체 인상 NumPy와하지
in the in the computation grass then we can actually computer these outputs
계산 잔디에서 다음 우리가 할 수 실제로 컴퓨터 이러한 출력에
symbolically so XY and Z are these symbolic things and we can compute ab&c
XY 및 Z는이 상징적 인 일이며 우리는 AB & C를 계산할 수 있습니다 상징적 있도록
just using these overloaded operators and that'll be building up this
바로 이러한 오버로드 된 연산자를 사용하고이를 구축 할 수 있습니다
computational graph in the background then once we've built up our
우리가 구축 한 후, 일단 백그라운드에서 계산 그래프 우리
computational craft we actually want to be able to run certain parts of it on
계산 공예 우리는 사실에 그것의 특정 부분을 실행할 수 있도록하려면
real data so we call this the anode odd function thing so this is saying about
실제 데이터는 그래서 우리는 그래서이 약 말하고있는이 양극 이상한 함수 일 전화
we want to take our function will take inputs XY and Z and it'll produce
우리는 입력 XY 및 Z를 취할 것입니다 우리의 기능을 할 그것을 생산합니다
outputs see this will return an actual python function that we can evaluate on
출력이 우리가 평가할 수있는 실제 파이썬 함수를 반환합니다 참조
real data and I'd like to point out that this is really where all the magic and
실제 데이터와 나는이 정말 지적하고 싶은 경우 모든 마법과
Fionna was happening that when you call the function it can be doing crazy crazy
Fionna 당신이 함수를 호출 할 때 미친 미친 일을 할 수 있다는 일어나고
things it can simplify your computational graph to make it more
물건은 그것이 더 확인하기 위해 계산 그래프를 단순화 할 수 있습니다
efficient it can actually symbolically divider I pretense and other things and
효율적인 실제로 상징적 내가 가식과 다른 것들과 산기 수 있습니다
it can actually generate native code so when you call function to connect it
당신이 그것을 연결하는 함수를 호출 할 때 실제로 그렇게 네이티브 코드를 생성 할 수 있습니다
actually sometimes compiled code on the flights are unofficially on the GPU so
실제로 때로는 항공편에서 코드를 컴파일 때문에 GPU에 비공식적 있습니다
all the magic and Fiano is really coming from this from this little innocent
모든 마법과 Fiano 정말이 작은 죄에서이오고있다
looking statement in Python but there's a lot going on under the hood here and
파이썬에서 문을 찾고 있지만 여기에 후드 일이 많이있다 및
now once we've gotten this magic function through all this crazy stuff
지금 한 번 우리는이 미친 물건을 통해이 마법의 기능을 쪘
then we can just run it on actual number higher raise so here we instantiate
우리는 단지 우리가 인스턴스화 그래서 여기 인상보다 실제 수에서 실행할 수 있습니다
xxyyxx easy as actual as actual number higher grades and then we can just about
xxyyxx 실제 수보다 높은 등급으로 실제 쉽고 그 다음 우리는 막을 수
our function and passing these actual number is to get the values out and this
이러한 실제 번호를 전달하는 우리의 기능은 이것을 값을 얻을 수 있습니다
is doing the same thing as doing these computations explosively in Python
파이썬에서 폭발적으로 이러한 계산을하고 같은 일을하고있다
except that the final version could be much more efficient due to all the magic
것을 제외하고 최종 버전으로 인해 모든 마법에 훨씬 더 효율적이 될 수
under the hood and piano version actually could be running on the GPU if
후드와 피아노 버전에서 실제로 GPU 경우에 실행 될 수있다
you have not configured but unfortunately we don't really care about
당신은 구성하지 않은 그러나 불행하게도 우리가 정말 걱정하지 않는다
computing things like this we wanted to know thats so here's an example of a
우리가 여기 먹으 렴 알고 싶어이 같은 일을 계산하는 것은의 예
simple tool air balloon at 10 so the idea is the same that we're going to
(10)에서 간단한 도구 공기 풍선 그래서 아이디어는 우리가 가고있는이 동일하다
declare our inputs but now instead of just XY and Z we have our input syntax
우리의 입력을 선언하지만 지금은 대신 그냥 XY 및 Z 우리가 우리의 입력 구문
our labels and Y which are better
더 나은 우리의 라벨 및 Y
are to weight matrices W&W too so we're just sort of setting up these symbolic
행렬 W & W 너무 그래서 우리는 그저 설정하는이 상징적 인 체중한다
variables that will be elements in our computational grass now 44 pass we it
변수는 우리의 계산 잔디의 요소가 될 것이다 지금 44 패스 우리를
looks kinda like numpy but it's not bizarre operations on the symbolic
좀 NumPy와 같습니다하지만 기호에없는 기괴한 작업이다
objects that are building up the graph in the background so here computing
그래서 여기 백그라운드에서 그래프를 구축 계산되는 개체
activations with this . method that is matrix multiply but we need symbolic
이과 활성화. 방법 행렬 곱셈하지만 우리는 상징적 필요가
objects we're doing a real issue using this this library function and we're
개체는 우리는이 라이브러리 함수를 사용하여 실제 문제를하고있는 우리는있어
doing another matrix multiply and then we can actually compute the loss the
또 다른 행렬의 곱셈을하고 우리는 실제로 손실을 계산할 수 있습니다
probabilities and the Los using a couple other library functions and again these
다시 이러한 몇 가지 다른 라이브러리 기능을 이용하여 확률과 로스
are all operations on the symbolic objects that are building up the
까지 구축하고 상징적 인 개체에 대한 모든 작업은
computational grass so that we can just compiled this function so our function
우리는 우리의 기능 때문에이 기능을 컴파일 할 수 있도록 전산 잔디
is going to take our data are labels and are 28 factor in our to weight matrices
걸릴 것입니다 우리의 데이터는 레이블이며, 행렬을 가중하는 우리의 28 요소는
and puts and as outputs I will return the loss and a scalar and our
및 풋 출력으로 나는 손실과 스칼라 우리를 반환합니다
classification scores in a vector and now we can run this thing on real data
분류 점수 벡터에서 지금 우리가 실제 데이터에이 일을 실행할 수 있습니다
just like we saw in the previous slide we can instantiate some actual number I
우리는 이전 슬라이드에서 본 것처럼 우리는 몇 가지 실제 수의 I를 인스턴스화 할 수
raised and then passed to the function so this is great but this is only the
함수에 제기하고 전달 그래서 이것은 큰하지만 이것은 단지입니다
fourth pass actually to be able to train this network and computer radiance so
네 번째는 실제로 그렇게이 네트워크 및 컴퓨터 생기를 양성 할 수 있도록
here we just need to add a couple lines of code to do that so this is the same
여기에 우리가 너무이 동일하다고 할 코드의 몇 라인을 추가 할 필요가
as before we're so we're defining are symbolic variables for our inputs and
우리는 우리가 정의하고있어 이전과 같이 우리의 입에 대한 상징적 인 변수는
our weights and so forth and we're combining
우리의 무게 등 우리는 함께있어
running the same four passes before to compute the loss to the computer law
전에 같은 4 패스를 실행하는 컴퓨터의 법률에 손실을 계산하기
symbolically know the difference is that we actually can do
상징적으로 차이가 우리가 실제로 할 수있는 알고
symbolic differentiation here so this is Dee W one and TW to we're telling the I
여기에 상징적 인 차별화 그래서이에 우리가 내가 말하는 거 야 디 W 하나 TW입니다
know that we want those to be the gradient of the ingredients of the loss
우리가 그는 손실의 성분의 기울기가되고 싶어요 것을 알고있다
with respect to those other symbolic variables W one Min W two so this is
그래서이 두 개의 W 하나의 최소 W 그 다른 상징적 인 변수에 대하여
really cool
정말 멋진
fiato just lets you take arbitrary gradients of any part of the graph with
fiato는 그래프의 어떤 부분에 임의의 그라데이션을 할 수 있습니다
respect to any other part of the graph not introduce introduced those as new
그래프의 다른 부분에 대한 새로운으로 그 도입 도입하지
symbolic variables in the graph so that you can really go crazy with that but
그래프의 기호 변수는 당신이 정말로 그와 함께 미친 갈 수 있도록하지만,
here in this case we're just gonna return those Canadians as outputs so now
여기이 경우 우리는 지금 출력으로 그 캐나다인을 반환거야
we're gonna compile a new function that again is going to take our inputs are
우리는 다시 새로운 기능을 컴파일거야 우리의 입력이 걸릴 것입니다
input input pixel sacks and our labels why along with the 28 matrices
입력 입력 픽셀 자루와 우리의 레이블 왜 28 행렬과 함께
and now it's going to return our loss the classification scores and also these
지금은 우리의 손실을 반환 할 것 이러한 분류 점수와
two ingredients so now we can actually use this setup to train a very simple
지금 우리는 실제로 매우 간단한 훈련이 설정을 사용할 수있는 두 가지 성분 있도록
neural network so we can actually just use gradient descent implement gradient
신경 네트워크는 그래​​서 우리는 실제로 단지 그라데이션을 구현 그라데이션 하강을 사용할 수 있습니다
descent in just a couple lines using using this this using this computation
이 계산을 사용하여이이를 이용하여 단지 몇 줄의 하강
grass so here we're
그래서 여기에 우리가있어 잔디
instantiating actual number higher raise for the data set and the factors and
데이터 세트 및 요인에 대한 인상보다 실제 수를 인스턴스화
some random matrices as again
로 다시 어떤 임의의 행렬
actual number higher raise and now every time we make this call to ask when we
실제 수는 더 높은 올릴 때 우리는 지금 우리가이 전화를 걸 때마다 물어
get back
돌아 가야
numpy array is containing a loss and the scores and the gradients so now that we
NumPy와 배열은 지금 우리가 그 손실 및 점수와 그라데이션을 포함한다
have the gradients we can just make a simple gradient update on our weights
그라디언트를 우리는 단지 간단한 그라데이션 업데이트를 우리의 가중치에 만들 수 있습니다
and measures promised an alley-oop to train our network but there's actually a
및 조치는 우리의 네트워크를 훈련 골목 - OOP를 약속하지만 실제로있다
big of a problem with this especially if you're running on a GPU anyone can
이 문제의 큰 당신이 할 수있는 GPU를 누군가에 실행중인 특히
anyone want totally lost the problem is that this is actually incurring a lot of
완전히 문제를 손실 할 사람이 실제로 많이 초래된다는 것이다
over communication overhead between the CPU and GPU because every time we we
CPU와 GPU 사이의 통신 오버 헤드를 통해 때문에 우리가 우리 때마다
call this a function and we get back these gradients thats copying the
기능이 전화 그리고 우리는 복사 먹으 렴 다시이 그라디언트를 얻을 수
gradients from the GPU back to the CPU and I can be an expensive operation and
다시 CPU에 GPU에서 그라디언트 나는 비용이 많이 드는 작업 할 수 있고,
now we're actually making our gradient stop this is CPU computation in numpy so
이제 우리는 실제로 우리의 그라데이션 중지 만들고있어이 너무 NumPy와의 CPU 계산이다
it would be really nice if we can make those gradient updates to our parameters
우리가 그 기울기 업데이트를 우리의 매개 변수를 할 수 있도록 할 수 있다면 정말 좋을 텐데
actually directly on the GPU and the way that we do that in Fiano is this with
실제로 직접 GPU 길에 우리가 그 Fiano이 함께 있음
with this school thing called a shared variable so I shared variable is another
공유 변수라고이 학교 일에 그래서 변수가 다른 것입니다 공유
part of the network that actually is a value that lives inside the computation
네트워크 실제로 일부는 내부 연산 사는 값
craft and actually persists from call to call so here this is this is actually
공예 실제로이 실제로이 그래서 여기에 전화 통화에서 지속
quite similar to before that now were defining our same symbolic variables X&Y
매우 유사 이제 정의 된 우리 같은 상징적 인 변수 X & Y 전
for the data and labels and now we're defining a couple of these new funky
데이터와 라벨과 지금 우리가 새로운 펑키의 몇 가지를 정의하고 대한
things funky shared variables for our to weight matrices and the initializing
행렬 및 초기화를 가중하는 우리를위한 것 펑키 공유 변수를
these weight matrices with numpy raised and now this is the same as before this
NumPy와 이러한 가중치 행렬을 제기하고 지금이 이전과 동일
is the exact same code as before where computing the forward pass using these
이들을 사용하여 포워드 패스를 산출 여기서 이전과 동일한 코드이다
library functions are symbolically
라이브러리 함수는 상징적이다
gradients but now the difference is in how we define our function so now this
그라디언트 그러나 우리는 지금이 그래서 우리의 함수를 정의하는 방법을 지금의 차이에
compiled function
컴파일 기능
only receives does not receive the weights and puts those actually live
만 가중치를 수신하지 않는 수신하고 그 실제로 살고 둔다
inside the computational graph instead we just received the data and the data
연산 그래프 내부 대신 우리는 단지 데이터 및 상기 수신 데이터
and the labels and now we are going to put the loss rather than output
그리고 라벨과 지금 우리는 출력보다 오히려 손실을 넣어 가고있다
ingredients explicitly and instead we actually provide these update rules they
성분은 명시 적으로 대신 우리가 실제로 이러한 업데이트 규칙을 제공하는 그들
should be run every time the function is called so these update rules notice our
이 업데이트 규칙을 알 수 있도록 함수가 호출 될 때마다 실행해야 우리
little functions that operate on the symbolic variables so this is just
이 그냥 그래서 상징적 인 변수에서 작동 작은 기능
saying that we should make he's creating the Santa stops to update W one Min W
우리는 그가 산타를 만드는 것해야한다는 것은 하나의 최소 W W 업데이트 할 중지
two every time we run this computational graph so writes weekly update and now to
이 우리가이 계산 그래프를 실행할 때마다 그래서 지금 매주 업데이트 및 기록
train this network all we need to do is call this function repeatedly and every
우리가해야 할 모든 반복마다이 함수를 호출 인이 네트워크를 훈련
time we call the function those will make a gradient stop on the way it's so
우리가 함수를 호출 할 때 사람들은 그렇게의 방법에 그라데이션 중지 할 것
we can just trying this network by just calling this thing repeatedly on in
우리는 그냥 반복해서 그냥이 일을 호출하여이 네트워크를 시도 할 수 있습니다
practice when you make when you're doing this kind of thing and I know you'll
당신이 이런 종류의 일을 할 때 할 때 연습하고 난 당신거야 알고
often define our training function call that update the weights and then also
종종 다음 무게를 업데이트하고 우리의 교육 함수 호출을 정의
evaluate function that I'll just put the scores and not make any updates you can
난 그냥 점수를 넣어 당신이 할 수있는 업데이트를하지거야 기능을 평가
actually have multiple of these compiled functions that about eight different
실제로이 컴파일 된 함수의 여러에 대한 8 개의 다른 것이있다
parts of the same graph yeah yeah yeah the question is how we compute gradients
같은 그래프의 부분은 그래 그래 문제는 우리가 기울기를 계산하는 방법이다
and it actually does it symbolically sort of person out the S well it's not
그것은 실제로는 그렇지 않아 잘은 상징적 종류의 사람이 밖으로에게 S 않습니다
actually person at the St because every time you make these calls it's a sort of
때마다 당신이이 통화를 할 수 있기 때문에 실제로 성에서 사람이의 일종이다
building up this computation on graphics object and then you can compute
그래픽 객체에이 계산을 구축하고 당신은 계산할 수 있습니다
gradients by just adding nodes onto the computation on graphics object so yeah
단지 그래픽의 계산에 노드를 추가하여 그라디언트 그래서 개체 그래
yeah so it needs to know every of these basic operators it knows what the
그래, 그래서 그것이 무엇을 알고 이러한 기본 운영자의 각을 알 필요가
derivative with the derivative is and it's still the normal normal have a
파생 상품과 파생 및이 여전히 정상 정상
back-propagation that you'll see it works but some of it but the pitch with
당신이 그것을 볼 것을 다시 전파는 작동하지만 그 중 일부하지만 피치
the I know is that it works and he's very very low level basic operations
내가 아는 그것이 작동하고 그는 매우 매우 낮은 수준의 기본 작업입니다
like these elements things and matrix multiply as and when it is hoping that
이러한 요소의 사물과 행렬 곱셈으로하고 바라고 때처럼
it can compile efficient code the combine those and simplify it
이 효율적인 코드를 컴파일 할 수있는 사람들을 통합하고 단순화
symbolically and that I'm not sure how well it works but that's at least what
상징적으로 내가 어떻게 작동하는지 잘 모르겠어요하지만 적어도 무슨하다고
they claim to do so there's a lot of a lot of other advanced things that you
그들은 그렇게 다른 고급 많은 것들을 많이 거기에 이렇게 주장하는 당신
can do anything I know that we just don't have time to talk about you can
무엇이든 할 수 나는 우리가 당신이 할 수있는 얘기 할 시간이없는 것을 알고있다
actually include conditionals directly inside your competition craft using
실제로 사용하여 경쟁 공예 내부에 직접 조건문은 다음과 같습니다
these files
이 파일
and switch commands you can actually include loops insider computational
그리고 스위치는 당신이 실제로 루프를 내부자 계산을 포함 할 수 있습니다 명령
graph using this this funny scan function that I don't really understand
그래프이 정말 이해하지 못하는이 재미 스캔 기능을 사용하여
but it's tough but theoretically it lets you implement recurrent networks quite
하지만 힘든하지만 이론적으로는 매우 재발 네트워크를 구현할 수 있습니다
easily as you can imagine for a moment are occurring at work in one of these
쉽게 당신이 잠시 상상할 수있는 다음 중 하나의 작업에서 발생하는
computational crafts all you're doing is passing the same weight matrix into
계산 공예가에 동일한 가중치 행렬을 통과하고있는 모든
multiple nodes and scan actually lets you sort of do that in a loop and have
여러 노드 및 정렬 할 그 루프 및이 수 실제로 검사
the loop be part of an explicit part of the graph and we can actually go crazy
루프는 그래프의 명시 적 부분의 일부와 우리가 실제로 미친 갈 수 있습니다
with derivatives we can compute derivatives with respect with out any
파생 상품과 우리는 밖으로 어떤과 ​​관련하여 파생 상품을 계산할 수 있습니다
part of the craft with respect to any other part we can also compute jacoby
우리는 또한 자코비 계산할 수있는 다른 부분에 대한 선박의 일부
ends by computing derivatives of derivatives we can use Allen our
파생 상품 우리는 알렌을 사용할 수의 파생 상품을 계산하여 종료 우리
operators to officially do made big major matrix-vector multiply as actors
운영자는 공식적으로 배우로서 큰 주요 행렬 - 벡터 곱셈을 만든하려면
and Jacoby Jones you can do a lot of pretty cool different derivative take
와 자코비 존스 당신은 정말 멋진 다른 파생 테이크를 많이 할 수
stock in piano that's maybe top and other frameworks and it also has some
아마 상단과 다른 프레임 워크 그리고 그것은 또한 일부가 피아노에 재고
support for sparse matrices it tries to optimize your code on the fly
스파 스 매트릭스에 대한 지원은 즉석에서 코드를 최적화하기 위해 시도
do some other cool things I know does have multi GPU support there's this
내가 아는 다른 멋진 일을하는 것은이 거기에 멀티 GPU 지원을 가지고
package that I have not used but that claims that you can get data parallelism
내가 그 제외한 사용하지 않은 패키지는 데이터 병렬 처리를 얻을 수 있다고 주장
so distribute I mean about to split up over multiple GPUs and there's
그래서 여러 GPU를 통해 분할에 대한 의미와 거기에 배포
experimental support for model parallelism with this computational
이 계산에 모델 병렬 처리에 대한 실험 지원
graph will be divided among the different devices but the documentation
그래프는 다른 장치 있지만 문서 사이에 분할됩니다
says its experimental so it probably really experimental so so you saw and
라고 그 실험 아마 정말 실험 그래서, 그래서 당신이 본 있도록
when working with the I know that the API is little bit low level and we need
작업을 할 때 나는 API가 조금 낮은 수준 인 것을 알고 우리는 필요
to sort of implement the update rules and everything ourself somos anya is
일종의 해결할은 somos 아냐가 업데이트 규칙과 모든 것을 구현
this high-level wrapper around the I know that sort of abstract away some of
는 I 주변이 높은 수준의 래퍼는 거리의 일부를 추상의 종류를 알고
those details for you so again we're sort of defining symbolic matrices and
당신을 위해 그 세부 그래서 다시 우리가 일종의 상징적 인 행렬을 정의하고 있고
lasagna now has these layer functions that will automatically set up the
라자냐는 자동으로 설정됩니다 이러한 계층 기능이있는
shared variables and that sort of thing we can compute the probability in the
공유 변수와 그런 종류의 물건 우리는의 확률을 계산할 수 있습니다
loss using these convenient things from the library and lasagna can actually
손실 라이브러리에서이 편리한 것을 사용하고, 라자냐 실제로 수
write these update rules for us to implement and a strong momentum and
우리가 구현하는 이러한 업데이트 규칙과 강한 추진력을 작성하고
other fancy things and now when we compile our function we actually just
다른 멋진 것들과 지금 우리가 컴파일 우리의 기능 우리가 실제로 단지
pass on these update rules that were written for us by my lasagna and all of
내 라자냐와 모두가 우리를 위해 기록 된이 업데이트 규칙에 전달
the way
방법
objects were taken care of taken care of for us by lasagna as well
객체뿐만 아니라 라자냐가 우리를 위해 찍은 치료의 치료를 찍은
and then at the end of the day we just end up with one of these compiled piano
다음 날의 끝에서 우리는 이러한 컴파일 피아노 하나 결국
functions and we use at the same way as before there's another there's another
기능과 우리는 또 다른 거기에 다른 거기에 이전과 같은 방법으로 사용
rapper 4390 that's pretty popular culture us which is a little bit is even
꽤 인기있는 문화의 래퍼 4390 우리는 조금 짝수되는
more high-level so here we're having making a sequential container and adding
그래서 여기에 우리가 순차적으로 컨테이너를 만들고 추가하는 데있어 더 높은 수준의
a stack of layers to it so this is kind of like torch and now we're having this
그것에 층의 스택은 그래서 이것은 종류의 횃불처럼 이제 우리는이 데있어
making this Sgt object that is going to actually updates for us and now we can
가는이 상사 개체를 만들기에 실제로 우리를 갱신하고 지금 우리가 할 수있는
train our network by just using the model that fit method so this is super
이 슈퍼 그래서 그냥 방법을 맞는 모델을 사용하여 우리의 네트워크를 훈련
high level and you can't even tell that using piano and in fact carry us well as
높은 수준의 당신은 심지어 피아노를 사용하여 실제로 우리를 수행 할뿐만 아니라 말할 수 없다
a background as well so you don't have to use the honor with it but there's
뿐만 아니라 당신이하지 않아도 배경은 그것으로 영광을 사용하지만 거기하기
actually one big problem with this piece of code and I don't know if you if you
당신이 당신의 경우 경우 실제로 하나의 큰이 코드 조각 문제와 나도 몰라
experience with ya know but this could actually crashes and it crashes in a
경험이 나중에 알고 있지만 실제로 충돌 수 있으며, 그것은에 충돌로
really bad way this is the error message so we get this giant stack trace none of
정말 나쁜 방법은 오류 메시지가 그렇습니다 우리는이 거대한 스택 트레이스 아무 것도 얻을
which is through any of the code that we wrote and we get this giant value error
우리가 작성한 코드의 통해 우리는이 거대한 값 오류가 발생하는
that doesn't make any sense to me so I'm not really an expert in Fiano so this
내가 Fiano 정말 전문가 그래서이 아니에요 그래서 나에게 어떤 의미가 없습니다
was really confusing to me so we wrote this kind of simple looking coating care
정말 나에게 혼란되었다 그래서 우리는 간단한 찾고 코팅 처리의이 종류를 썼다
us but because it's using fiato as a pack and it crapped out and gave us this
우리하지만 팩으로 fiato를 사용하고 그것을 밖으로 허튼과 우리에게 준 때문에
really confusing error message so that's i think one of the common pain points
즉, 내가 일반적인 통증 포인트 중 하나라고 생각, 그래서 정말 오류 메시지가 혼란
and failure cases with anything that uses as a background that debugging can
디버깅 배경으로 사용 아무것도 실패 사례 수
be kinda hard so like any good developer I googled the air and I found out that I
좀 열심히 공기를 봤와 나는 것을 발견 좋은 개발자가 같은 수
found out that I was including the width of the white variable wrong and I was
내가 잘못 흰색 변수의 폭을 포함하고 나는 것을 발견
supposed to use this other other function to convert my wife variable and
내 아내 변수로 변환이 기타 다른 기능을 사용하는 가정 및
make the problem go away but that was not obvious from the error message
문제가 멀리 갈 수 있도록하지만 오류 메시지에서 분명 아니었다
that's something to be good to be worried about when using piano piano
그 피아노 피아노를 사용할 때 신경이 쓰이는 것이 좋을 위해 뭔가
actually has preteen models so we talk about lasagna
우리가 라자냐에 대해 이야기 때문에 실제로 초반 이었죠 모델이
actually has a pretty good models you a lot of different popular model
실제로 꽤 좋은 모델 당신에게 다른 인기있는 모델을 많이 가지고
architecture is that you might want so in lasagna you can use Alex and Google
아키텍처는 당신이 그렇게 라자냐 당신이 알렉스와 구글을 사용 할 수도 있다는 것입니다
Matt and BG I don't think they have resident yet but they have quite a lot
매트와 BG 나는 그들이 아직 주민을 생각하지 않습니다하지만 그들은 꽤 많이있다
of useful things there and there are a couple other packages I found that the
거기에 유용한 것들과 내가 발견 몇 가지 다른 패키지가
obvious that really seems good except I mean this was clearly awesome because it
분명 정말로 내 말을 제외하고이 명확하게 굉장했다 좋은 것 같다 그것 때문에
was a cs2 31 and project from last year
작년부터 CS2 (31) 및 프로젝트였다
but if your gonna pick one i think probably the lasagna models it was
당신거야 하나를 선택하면하지만 난 그것이 아마 라자냐 모델을 생각한다
really good so from my one day experience of playing with the I know
내가 아는 가지고 노는 내 하루 경험 그래서 정말 좋은
about pros and cons that I could see where that its its pipeline an umpire's
장점과 단점에 대해 나는 곳의 파이프 라인이 심판의 볼 수있는
that's great
훌륭 해요
this computational crap seems like a really powerful idea especially around
이 계산 쓰레기 특히 주위에 정말 강력한 아이디어처럼 보인다
computing gradient symbolically and all these optimizations it especially with R
상징적으로 그라데이션을 계산하고 이러한 모든 최적화 그것은 특히 R과
and ends I think would be much easier to implement using this computational graph
나는이 계산 그래프를 사용하여 구현하는 것이 훨씬 쉬울 것이라고 생각 종료
Rottino is kind of ugly and gross but especially lasagna looks pretty good to
Rottino의 종류 추한 및 총하지만 특히 라자냐는 꽤 좋아 보인다
me and sort of takes away some of the pain the error messages can be pretty
저와 종류의 오류 메시지가 꽤 될 수있는 고통의 일부를 빼앗아
painful as we saw and big models from what I've heard can have really long
내가 무슨 소리를 들었어요에서 우리가 보았 듯이 고통과 큰 모델은 정말 오래 할 수 있습니다
compile times so that that when we're compiling that function on the fly for
컴파일 시간 그래서 그 우리에 대한 즉시 해당 함수를 컴파일 할 때
all these simple examples that pretty much runs instantaneously but we're
거의 순간적으로 실행되는 모든 간단한 예제하지만 우리는있어
doing big complicated things like neural Turing machines I've heard stories that
내가 이야기를 들었습니다 신경 튜링 기계처럼 큰 복잡한 일을 그
that could actually take maybe half an hour to compile so that's that's not
즉, 실제로는 아니에요 그건 너무 컴파일 아마 반 시간이 걸릴 수 있습니다
good and that's not good for iterating quickly on your models and another sort
좋은 그것은 당신의 모델과 다른 종류에 빠르게 반복에 대한 좋지 않다
of pain point is that the API is much better than torch that it's doing all
통증의 포인트는 API가 모든 일을거야 토치보다 훨씬 더 나은 것입니다
this complicated stuff in the background so it's kind of hard to understand and
그것은 이해하기 힘든 종류, 그래서 배경이 복잡한 물건과
debug but actually happening to your code and then preteen models are maybe
디버그하지만, 실제로 코드를 발생하고 초반 이었죠 모델은 어쩌면이다
not quite as good as cafe or torch but it looks like lasagna is pretty good
라자냐는 꽤 좋은처럼되지 확실히 카페 또는 토치 좋은 그러나 그것은 본다
ok so we've got fifteen minutes now to talk about 1000 although first if
확인은 그래서 우리는 첫 번째 경우 비록 1000을 얘기 십오분 지금있어
there's any questions about the I know I can try ok that's not so tenser flow
내가 시도 할 수 있습니다 알고는 확인이 그렇게 tenser 흐름이 아니다에 대한 질문이있다
sensor flows from Google it's really cool and shiny and new and everyone's
센서는 정말 시원하고 반짝 새롭고의 Google에서 모든 사람의 흐름
excited about it and it's actually very similar to Fiona in a lot of ways that
그것에 대해 흥분하고 실제로 많은 방법에서 피오나와 매우 유사 그
they're really taking this idea of a computational graph and a building on
그들은 정말 계산 그래프의이 아이디어와 건물을 복용하고
that for everything so tenser flow and Fiano actually very very closely linked
그는 모든 것을 tenser 흐름과 Fiano 실제로 아주 아주 밀접하게 연결되도록
in my mind and that's sort of like harris can get away with using either
내 마음에 그 중 하나를 사용하여 멀리 얻을 수있는 종류의 해리스 등이다
one is a backhand and also kind of one maybe point to make about 1000 is that
하나는 백핸드이며, 또한 어떤 하나의 어쩌면 약 1000인지 확인 가리
it's sort of the first one of these frameworks that was designed from the
그것은에서 설계된 이러한 프레임 워크 중 제 1의 일종
ground up by professional engineers
전문 엔지니어에 의해 접지
so a lot of other frameworks sort of spun out of academic research labs and
그래서 다른 프레임 워크의 많은 종류의 학술 연구 실험실에서 회전 및
they're really great and they let you do things really well but they were sort of
그들은 정말 좋은있어, 그들은 당신이 정말 잘 일을 할 수 있도록하지만 그들은 일종의했다
maintained by grad students especially so torch especially is maintained by
토치 특히 의해 관리되고, 특히 있도록 대학원 학생들에 의해 유지
some engineers at Twitter and Facebook now but it was originally an academic
지금 트위터와 페이스 북에서 일부 엔지니어하지만 원래 학술했다
project and for all of these I think tenser flow was the first one that was
프로젝트 및 이들의 모든 나는 tenser 흐름이었다 첫 번째 생각
from the ground up from a neck from an industrial place so maybe theoretically
그래서 아마 이론적으로 산업 곳에서 목에서 처음부터
that could lead to better code quality or test coverage or something i dont no
그없이 내가 그나마 나은 코드 품질이나 시험 범위 또는 무언가로 이어질 수
I'm not sure seemed pretty scary so here's so here's our favorite to lay
나는 확실하지 그래서 여기에 꽤 무서운 듯 우리 마음에 드는 사람이 누워있어 여기 그래서 해요
rabin that we're gonna we did it and all other frameworks let's do it intends to
우리는거야 라빈 우리는 그것을했고, 다른 모든 프레임 워크는 의도의이하자
flow so this is actually really similar to the I know so you can see that we're
그래서 우리가 걸 볼 수 있도록이 실제로 알고있는 나는 정말 비슷합니다 흐름
importing tenser flow and in Fiano remember we have these matrix and vector
Fiano에 tenser 흐름을 가져 우리가이 행렬과 벡터를 기억
symbolic variables intense workload they're called placeholders but it's the
기호 변수 강렬한 워크로드 그들은 자리라고하고 있지만입니다
same idea these are just creating input nodes in our computational graph we're
이 같은 생각은 우리가있어 우리의 계산 그래프에 입력 노드를 작성하는
also going to define the weight matrices in fiato we have these shared things
또한 fiato에 무게 행렬을 정의하는 것 우리는 이러한 공유 일이
that lived inside the computation graph same idea and tensor flexible called
그라는 계산 그래프 같은 생각하고 유연한 텐서 안에 살았다
variables we just like just like in Ciano be computed are forward pass using
변수를 우리가 같은 단지 계산 Ciano처럼 사용하여 통과 기대된다
these library methods that operate operate on symbolically on these things
작동이 라이브러리 방법은이 일에 상징적에 작동
and build up a computational graph so that lets you easily compute the
즉, 쉽게를 계산 할 수 있도록 전산 그래프를 구축
probability is on the loss and everything like that symbolically this
확률은 상징적으로이 같은 손실과 모든에
actually I think to me looks more like care us rather looks a little bit more
실제로 나는 나보다는 조금 더 우리에게 보이는 관심이 더 많은 것 같습니다에 생각
like carousel lasagna than rocky I know but we're using this gradient descent
바위보다 회전 목마 라자냐처럼 알고 있지만, 우리는이 경사 하강을 사용하는
optimizer and we're telling it to minimize the loss so here we're not
최적화는 그리고 우리는 그래서 여기에 우리가하지 않은 손실을 최소화하기 위해 그것을 말하는 거
explicitly but spitting out gradients and we're not explicitly writing about
명시 적으로하지만, 그라디언트를 토하고 우리는 명시 적으로 대해 서면으로하지 않는
trading update rules were instead using this people thing but just sort of adds
무역 업데이트 규칙 대신이 사람들의 일을 사용하지만 그냥 일종의 추가되었다
whatever it needs to into the graph in order to minimize that loss and now just
그냥 지금 손실을 최소화하기 위해 그래프로 할 필요가 무엇이든
like in Ciano market we can actually instantiate using actual number higher
같은 Ciano 시장에서 우리가 실제로 더 높은 실제 번호를 사용하여 인스턴스화 할 수
raise
증가
some some small datasets and then we can run in the loop so intense air flow and
일부 몇 가지 작은 데이터 세트 후 우리는 루프 너무 강한 공기 흐름에서 실행할 수 있으며,
you actually want to run your code you need to use you need to wrap it in this
당신은 실제로 당신이 그것을 포장 할 필요가 사용해야하는 코드를 실행하려면
session code I don't understand what's doing but it's you had to do it actually
세션 코드는 내가 무엇을하고 있는지 이해가 안하지만 그건 당신이 실제로 그것을 할 수 있었다
went to do although actually what it's doing is that all the stops short of
실제로 무엇을하고있어하면 그 모든 정거장 짧은하지만 할 갔다
setting up your computational grass and the missed session is actually doing
당신의 계산 잔디를 설정하고 놓친 세션이 실제로하고있다
whatever optimization it needs to actually like to run it
어떤 최적화 실제로 실행하고자 할 필요가
yeah yeah so if you're so the question is what is one hot so if you remember in
그래 그래서 당신이 있다면 그래서 질문은 당신이 기억 그래서 만약 하나의 뜨거운 무엇인가
your assignments when you did like a soft max loss function but why was
과제는 부드러운 최대 손실 함수처럼했지만 왜 때
always an integer telling you which thing you wanted but in some of these
항상 정수는 당신이 원하는하지만 어떤 일을 말하는 이들 중 일부에
frameworks instead of an integer it should be a factor where everything is
모든 곳에 대신 정수의 프레임 워크는 요인이 될한다
zero except for the one that was the credit class so that was actually the
즉 실제로이었을 정도로 신용 클래스가 있던 일을 제외하고 제로
bug that tripped me up on care us back there was the difference between one hot
에 나를 넘어 버그는 차이가 뜨거운 일 사이에 있었다 다시 우리를 걱정
and not one hot and it turns out 10 2011 hot whatever right so than when we
뜨거운 그것은 10 2011 핫 어떤 권리를 밝혀없는 것보다 우리 때
actually want to train this network then we call in fiato remember we actually
실제로 우리가 실제로 기억하고 우리가 fiato에 전화 한 후이 네트워크를 훈련 할
compiled this function object and then call the function over and over again
이 함수 객체를 컴파일 한 다음 또 다시 함수를 호출
the equivalent intense air flow is that we used to call the run method on the
해당 강한 공기 흐름은 우리가의 run 메소드를 호출하는 데 사용한다는 것입니다
session object and we tell it what switch output we wanted to compute so
세션 객체 우리는 우리가 계산하는 원한 스위치 출력을 말해
here we're telling it that we want to compute the train stopped out what I'm a
여기에서 우리는 우리가 기차가 내가이야 무엇을 중단 계산 할 것인지를 말하는 거
la Salle putt and we're gonna feed at these numpy raised into these inputs so
라 셀리 퍼트 우리는 이러한 입력에 발생이 NumPy와에 거 피드있어 그렇게
this is kind of the same idea as Diano except we're just calling the run method
우리가 run 메소드를 호출하는 것을 제외하고이 디아 노 같은 아이디어의 종류
rather than explicitly compiling compiling a function and in the process
오히려 명시 함수를 컴파일 컴파일보다 과정에서
of evaluating this train stop object election make a gradient descent on the
이 열차 정지 객체 선거을 평가에 그라데이션 하강을
weights so then we just run this thing in a loop and it'll the Los goes down
무게는 그래서 우리는 단지 루프에서이 일을 실행하고 로스가 다운 될 수 있습니다
and everything is beautiful so one of the really cool things about tenser flow
모든 것이 tenser 흐름에 대한 정말 멋진 것들 중 하나 아름답습니다 그래서
is this thing called tenser board that lets you easily easily visualize what's
쉽게 쉽게 무엇을 시각화 할 수 있습니다 tenser 보드라는이 일입니다
going on in your network so here is pretty much the same code that we had
그래서 여기에 네트워크에서 진행하는 것은 우리가 가진 거의 동일한 코드입니다
before except we've added these three little lines hopefully you can see it if
우리는 희망이 세 개의 작은 줄을 추가 한 제외하기 전에 경우를 볼 수 있습니다
not you'll have to trust me so here where computing a scalar summary of the
의 스칼라 요약을 계산하는 곳없는 당신은 그래서 여기에 저를 신뢰해야합니다
loss and that's giving us a new symbolic variables
손실 그것은 우리에게 새로운 상징적 인 변수를주고
law summary and more computing a histogram summary of the weight matrices
법의 개요 더욱 가중 행렬들의 히스토그램을 산출 요약
W on w-2 and also getting us new symbolic variables W one pissed and w2
화가 하나 W2 W 2 w도 우리에게 점점 새로운 상징적 인 변수에 W
hissed now we're getting another symbolic variable called emerged that
지금 우리가라는 또 다른 상징적 인 변수를 얻고 야유하는 것으로 나타났다
can emerge as all those summaries together using some magic I don't
함께 그렇게하지 ​​마법을 사용하는 모든 사람들 요약으로 부상 할 수 있습니다
understand and we're getting this summary writer object that we can use to
이해하고 우리는 우리가 사용할 수있는이 요약 작가 개체를 받고있어
actually dumped out those summaries to desk and now in our loop when we're
실제로 우리가있을 때 우리의 루프에서 지금 책상에 그 요약을 덤프하고
actually running the network then we tell it to evaluate to evaluate the
실제로 다음 네트워크를 실행 우리는을 평가하는 평가를 말해
training staff and a loss like before her at all so this merge summary object
교육 직원과 같은 손실 그녀의 모든 그래서이 병합 요약 개체 전에
so in the process of evaluating the splurge summary object it'll compute
그래서 과시 요약을 평가하는 프로세스에서 계산할 것이다 개체
gradient it'll compute histograms of the weights and dump those summaries to desk
이 가중치의 히스토그램을 계산합니다 그라데이션 책상에 그 요약을 덤프
and then we tell our writer to actually at the summaries I guess that's where
그리고, 우리는 요약에 내가 그 어디 같아요 실제로 우리의 작가에게
the right into this happens so once you run this thing then you get the mall
그 다음에이 일을 실행하면 사용자가 쇼핑몰을 얻을 수 있도록이에 대한 권리가 발생합니다
this thing is running it sort of constantly streaming all this
이 일을 지속적으로 정렬을 실행하는 모든이를 스트리밍
information about what's going on in your network to desk and then you just
책상에 네트워크에서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지에 대한 정보는 다음 당신은
start up this this web server that ships with tensor flow sensor board and we get
그 텐서 유량 센서 보드와 함께 제공되는이이 웹 서버를 시작하고 우리가 얻을
these beautiful beautiful visualisations about what's going on in your network so
그래서 당신의 네트워크에서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지에 대한이 아름다운 아름다운 시각화
here on the left
여기 왼쪽에
member we were telling we were getting a scalar summary of the loss so this
회원 우리는 우리가이 때문에 손실 스칼라 요약을 얻고 있었다 말하고 있었다
actually shows that loss was going down I mean it was a small it was a big
실제로 손실이 나는 그것이 큰 작은이었다 의미 내려가는 것을 보여줍니다
network and a small dataset but that means everything is working and this
네트워크 및 소규모 데이터 세트하지만 그 모든 의미가 작동이됩니다
over here on the right hand side showing you histograms over time showing you the
여기 오른쪽에 표시 당신은 당신을 보여주는 시간이 지남에 따라 히스토그램
distributions of the values in your weight matrices so this is the stuff is
당신의 체중 행렬의 값의 분포이 물건은 그래서
really really cool and I think this is a really really beautiful debugging tool
정말 정말 시원하고 나는이 정말 정말 아름다운 디버깅 도구라고 생각합니다
so when i when I've been working on projects and torch I've written this
내가 프로젝트와 토치 작업을했습니다 때 때 그래서 나는이 작성했습니다
kind of stuff myself by hand
종류의 손으로 자신을 물건
just kinda dumping JSON blobs out of torture and then writing my own custom
그냥 좀 고문에서 JSON의 모양을 덤핑하고 내 자신의 정의를 작성
visualization visualizer is to view these kind of statistics because they're
시각화 시각화은이기 때문에 통계의 이러한 종류를 볼 수 있습니다
really useful and with tents are you don't have to write any about yourself
정말 유용하고 텐트 당신은 자신에 대해 어떤을 작성하지 않아도됩니다으로
you just a couple lines of code to your training script run they're saying and
그들은 말을하는지 훈련 스크립트 실행에 코드를 사용하면 단지 몇 라인과
you can get all these beautiful visualisations to help your debugging
당신은이 모든 아름다운 시각화하여 디버깅 도움을 얻을 수 있습니다
tenser flow sensor board can also help you even visualize what your network
tenser 유량 센서 보드는 또한 당신도 어떤 네트워크 시각화 할 수 있습니다
structure looks like so here we've annotated are variables with these names
이 이름을 가진 변수는 구조가 그래서 여기에 우리가 주석했던 모양이다
and now when we're doing the forward pass we can actually scope some of the
지금 우리는 우리가 범위 실제로 몇몇을 할 수있는 전진 패스를하고있는 경우
complications under a namespace and that sort of the slices group together
네임 스페이스와 함께 슬라이스 그룹의 종류에 따라 합병증
computations that
계산이
should belong together semantically now other than that it's the same with the
그것은과 동일합니다보다 함께 의미 지금 다른 속해야
same thing that we saw before and now if we run this network and load up tents or
우리가 전에 지금보고 같은 것은 우리가이 네트워크를 실행하고 텐트를로드하는 경우 또는
more and we can actually get this beautiful visualization for how like
더 우리가 실제로 어떻게 같은이 아름다운 시각화를 얻을 수 있습니다
what our network actually looks like and we can actually click and look and see
우리의 네트워크는 실제로처럼 보이는 우리가 실제로 클릭하고 찾아 볼 수있는
what the screens on the scores and really help debug what's going on inside
정말 무슨 점수에 화면 내부에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 디버그에 도움
this network and Egypt you see these loss and scores
이 네트워크 이집트 당신은 손실과 성적이 참조
these are the semantic namespaces that we defined it during the forward pass
이는 우리가 포워드 패스 중에 정의 된 의미있는 네임
and if we click on the scores for example it opens up and lets us see all
우리가 예를 들어 점수를 클릭하면 그것을 열어 우리 모두 볼 수 있습니다
the operations that have that up here inside the computation on graphics that
그래픽에 계산 내부 여기에를 가지고 작업하는
node so I thought this was really cool if it lets you like really easily debug
노드는 그래서 나는 정말 쉽게 디버그처럼 당신이 할 수 있다면 이것은 정말 멋진 줄 알았는데
what's going on inside your networks while it's running enough to write any
이 중 하나를 작성하는만큼 실행중인 동안 무슨 일이 당신의 네트워크 내부에서 무슨 일
of Apple's Asian code yourself so tender flow does have support from multi GPU so
애플의 아시아 코드로 자신을 너무 부드러운 흐름은 멀티 GPU 지원을해야합니까 그래서
has data parallelism like you might expect so I'd like to point out that
데이터 병렬 그렇게 예상처럼 나는 것을 지적하고 싶습니다있다
actually this distribute this distribution part is probably one of the
실제로는이 메일 부분은 아마도 중 하나입니다 배포
other major selling point sometimes a flow that it can try to actually
실제로 시도 할 수있는 다른 주요 판매 포인트는 때때로 흐름
distributed computation crap in different ways across different devices
다른 기기에서 다른 방법으로 분산 계산 쓰레기
and actually place the distribute that crap smartly to minimize communication
실제로 통신을 최소화하기 위해 기민하게 그 쓰레기를 분산 배치
overhead and so on so one thing that you can do is data parallelism where you
오버 헤드 등등 그래서 당신이 할 수있는 한 가지 데이터 병렬 어디에이다
just put your money back across different devices and run each one
단지 다른 기기에서 다시 돈을 넣어 각 하나를 실행
forward and backward and then either some of the gradients to do
전후 다음 중 하나 그라디언트 중 일부는해야 할 일
synchronous distributed training or just make a synchronous updates to your
단지에 동기 업데이트를하거나 동기 분산 교육 당신의
parameters and do a synchronous training buchanan the white paper claims she can
매개 변수와는 동기 훈련 뷰캐넌에게 그녀가 할 수있는 백서 주장을
do both of these things and tensor flow but I didn't I didn't try it out you can
이런 것들과 텐서 흐름의 양을하지만 나는 그것을 밖으로 당신이 할 수하지 않았다 않았다
also actually do model parallelism in intensive flow as well but lets you
또한 실제로뿐만 아니라 집중적 인 흐름 모델의 병렬 처리를 수행하지만 다음을 수행 할 수 있습니다
split up the same model and compute different parts of the same model on
같은 모델을 분할에 같은 모델의 다른 부분을 계산
different devices so here's an example so one place for that might be useful is
그래서 여기에 다른 장치는 그래서이 유용 할 수 있습니다 한 곳에는 예입니다
a multi-layer recurrent network there it might actually be a good idea to run
다층 재발 네트워크가 실제로 실행하는 것이 좋습니다 수 있습니다
different layers of a network on different CPUs because those things can
다른 CPU에서 네트워크의 다른 레이어 그 일을 할 수 있기 때문에
actually take a lot of memory so that's the type of thing that you can actually
그 물건의 종류가 그래서 실제로 많은 메모리를 가지고 당신은 실제로 수
do you can do that intense air flow without too much pain
당신은 너무 많은 고통없이 그 강한 공기 흐름을 할 수 않습니다
tenser flow is also the only of the frameworks that can run into distributed
tenser 흐름은 분산으로 실행할 수있는 프레임 워크의 유일한입니다
mode not just a strip across one machine and multiple GPUs but actually
하나의 시스템 및 다중 GPU를 실제로에서 모드뿐만 아니라 스트립
distribute them training model across many machine
그들에게 많은 기계에서 교육 모델을 배포
ads so the caveat here is that that part is not open source yet rated as of today
광고 여기서주의해야 할 점은 그 부분은 아직 오늘로 평가 오픈 소스 아니라고 그래서
the open source release of tensor flow can only do single machine multi GPU
텐서 흐름의 오픈 소스 버전은 단일 시스템 멀티 GPU 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다
training but I think but hopefully soon that part will be released to be really
훈련하지만 난 생각하지만 희망이 곧 그 부분은 정말로 발표 될 예정이다
cool right so here
바로 그래서 여기에 멋진
the idea is you can just end reply was aware of communication costs both
아이디어는 그냥 응답이 모두 통신 비용을 알고 있었다 끝낼 수있다
between GPU and CPU but also between different machines on the network so
네트워크에있는 다른 시스템 간의 또한 GPU와 CPU 만 사이에 그렇게
that it can try to smartly distribute the computation craft across different
그것은 현명 다른 걸쳐 계산 공예를 배포하려고 할 수 있습니다
machines and across different CPUs within those machines to compute
그 기계에서 다른 CPU에서 기계는 계산하기
everything as efficiently as possible so that's i think thats really cool and
모든 가능한 한 효율적으로 그 그래서 난 그게 정말 멋진 생각
that's something that the other frameworks just can't do right now one
즉 다른 프레임 워크가 바로 지금 일을 할 수없는 뭔가
can point with tens or flow is preteen models so I looked I did a thorough
수십 흐름을 가리킬 수 있습니다 것은 초반 이었죠 모델 나는 보았다 그래서 나는 철저한했다
Google search and the only thing I could come up with was an inception module a
구글은 검색과 내가 함께 올 수있는 유일한 방법은 처음 모듈가 있었다
pre-trial inception model but it's only accessible through this Android explore
사전 시험 개시 모델 만이 탐구 안드로이드를 통해 만 접근 가능
this and rate them all so that's something I would have expected to be
이 그들 있도록 모든 평가 내가 될 것으로 예상했을 것이다 뭔가
more clear documentation but that's at least you have that one pitch a model
명확한 문서가 더 있지만 그건 적어도 당신은 1 피치 모델이
either other than that I'm not I'm not really aware of other preteen models
그 중 하나가 아닌 다른 내가 다른 초반 이었죠 모델의 정말 알고 아니에요 아니에요
intense air flow but maybe maybe there are out maybe they're out there and I
강한 공기 흐름하지만 어쩌면 어쩌면 어쩌면 그들은 거기있어, 내가 거기에 있습니다
just don't know about them
그냥 모르는
prob says no so I googled correctly so that answer flow pros and cons
확률값은 그래서 제대로 봤하지 말합니다 그 대답 흐름 장점과 단점 때문에
again my quick one day experiment it's really good because its pipeline an
다시는 내 빠른 일일 실험 정말 좋은 파이프 라인의 때문에
umpire that's really cool I know it has this idea of computation on graphics
나는 그것이 그래픽에 대한 계산이 아이디어를 가지고 알고 정말 멋진 심판
which i think is super powerful and actually takes this idea of
이는 내가 슈퍼 강력 생각하고 실제로 이런 생각을합니다
computational graphs even farther than than Fiano really and things like
계산 그래프도 더 Fiano보다보다 정말와 같은 것들
checkpointing and distributing across devices these all end up as just know
검사 점 및 장치를 통해 배포 이러한 모든처럼 알고 결국
it's inside the computation on graphics 4000 that's really cool it's also claims
그것은 정말 멋진 그래픽 4000에 계산 내부의는 주장이다
to have much faster compile time something I know I've heard horror
더 빨리가 나는 공포를 들었습니다 알고 시간 뭔가를 컴파일
stories about neural tree machines taking half an hour to compile maybe
아마 컴파일 시간 반을 복용 신경 나무 기계에 대한 이야기
maybe that should be faster intends or flow so I've heard tenser board looks
어쩌면 그게 더 빠를 계획 또는 내가 들었어요 tenser 보드 외모 흐름한다
awesome that looks amazing I want to use that everywhere
놀라운 보이는 멋진 내가 사방에 그것을 사용하려면
it has really cool data and model model parallelism I think much more advanced
내가 훨씬 더 진보 된 생각 정말 멋진 데이터와 모델 모델 병렬 처리가
than the other frameworks although the distributed stop is still secret sauce
다른 프레임 워크보다 배포 중지는 여전히 비밀 소스 있지만
that Google but hopefully I'll come out to the rest of us eventually but I guess
구글 만 잘하면 나는 결국 우리의 나머지 부분에 나올거야하지만 난 생각하는 것이
as bob was saying it's even maybe the scariest code based actually dig into
밥이도 아마 실제로 기반 무서운 코드를 파고있어 말을 하였다으로
and understand what's working under the hood so at least my my fear about cancer
후드 암에 대해 너무 적어도 나의 두려움에서 일하고 이해
flow is that if you want to do some kind of crazy weird imperative code and you
흐름은 당신 미친 이상한 필수적 코드와 어떤 종류의 작업을 수행하려는 경우
cannot easily work it into their computational graph abstraction that
쉽게 계산 그래프 추상화로 작동하지 않을 수
seems like you could be in a lot of trouble we're in may be in in in torture
당신은 문제를 많이 될 수있는 것 같다 같은 것은 우리에있어 고문에에의 할 수있다
you can just write whatever imperative code you want inside the forward and
당신은 당신이 앞으로 내부에 원하는 필수적 어떤 코드를 작성할 수 있으며,
backward passes of your own custom theirs but that seems like the biggest a
이전 버전과 그들의 고유 한 사용자 정의의 패스하지만 가장 큰 유사한 것
worrying point for me about working with tons of law and practice another another
법의 톤 작업에 대한 나를 위해 점을 걱정하고 또 다른 연습
kind of awkward thing is the slack appreciate models so that's that's kind
어색한 일의 종류는 그 종류이다, 그래서 이완이 모델을 주셔서 감사하다
of gross
의 총
even installing on a 2002 was a little bit painful they claimed to have a
심지어 2002 년에 설치하는 것은 그들이이 주장 조금 아팠다
python we all that you can just download and install with PEP but it broke and I
파이썬은 우리 방금 다운로드 PEP에 설치할 수있는 모든하지만 파산 및 I
had to change the filename annually to get to install and then they had a
그리고 그들은했다 설치 얻기 위해 매년 파일 이름을 변경했다 및
broken dependency that I had to update manually and like download some random
내가 수동으로 업데이트했고, 같은 일부 랜덤를 다운로드 깨진 의존성
zip file and unpack it and copy some random files around but it eventually
zip 파일 그리고 그것은 결국 포장을 풀고 주위에 어떤 임의의 파일을 복사 할 수 있지만
worked but installation was tough even on my own machine that I have sudo 2012
일을하지만 설치 내가 sudo는 2012이 심지어 내 자신의 컴퓨터에 어려웠다
so they should get their act together on that so I put together this quick
그래서 그들은 내가 함께이 빨리 넣어 그 함께 자신의 행동을 얻어야한다
overview table that kind of covers when I think people would care about on major
나는 사람들이 주에 대한 관심이라고 생각하면 종류의 커버 개요 표
points between the frameworks whitewater languages what kinda preteen models are
좀 초반 이었죠 모델이 무엇인지 언어 급류 프레임 워크 사이의 점
available
유효한
question
문제
the question is is which of these support Windows I'm sorry but I don't
문제는 미안 이러한 지원 Windows의입니다하지만 난하지 않습니다
know
알고있다
I think you're on your own
난 당신이 자신에 있다고 생각
aww you can use AWS from Windows ok
앗 확인을 윈도우에서 AWS를 사용할 수 있습니다
ok so I put together this quick come quick comparison chart between the
확인 그래서 나는이 빠른 간의 빠른 비교 차트 와서 함께 넣어
frameworks that I think covers some of the major bullet points that people care
나는 사람들이 관심있는 주요 총알 포인트의 일부를 커버 생각 프레임 워크
about talking about what language is whether they have free trade models what
이야기에 대해 어떤 언어가 자유 무역 모델을 가지고 있는지 여부를 손쉽게
kind of parallelism you have and how readable as the source code and whether
당신이 병렬 처리의 종류와 방법을 읽을 수있는 소스 코드 등의 여부
they get our hands so I had a couple of use cases in let's see we've got holy
내가하자 참조에 사용 사례 몇 가지를 가지고, 그래서 그들은 우리가 거​​룩한있어 우리의 손을 얻을
crap we got 250 slides and we still have two minutes left so let's let's do let's
쓰레기 우리는 250 슬라이드를 얻었고, 우리는 여전히 이분은의이의이하자하자하자 그렇게 떠났다
play a little game suppose that all you wanted to do was extracted aleksandr BGG
약간의 게임은 당신이하고 싶었던 모든 알렉산드르의 BGG 추출한다고 가정 재생
features which framework would you pick
어떤 프레임 워크 기능은 당신이 선택할 것
yeah me too let's say all we wanted to do was find to an Alex net on on some
그래 내가 너무 일부에에 그물 알렉스를 찾을의 우리가하고 싶었던 모든 말을 하였다하자
new data yeah let's say we want to do image captioning with fine-tuning ok I
새로운 데이터는 그래의 우리가 미세 조정을 확인 I와 이미지 캡션을하고 싶은 말을하자
heard a good distribution so this is my thought process I'm not saying this is
좋은 분포를 들어 본 것은 그래서 이것은 내가이가 말하는 게 아니에요 내 생각 과정입니다
the right answer but the way I think about this is that for this problem we
나는 이것에 대해 생각하는 정답하지만 방법은 해당이 문제에 대한 우리
need preteen models preteen models were looking at Cafe or torture lasagna we
초반 이었죠 모델은 카페 나 고문 라자냐 우리보고 있었다 초반 이었죠 모델 필요
need our hands so kathy is pretty much out even though people have done have
캐시는 거의 밖으로 사람들이 할 경우에도, 그래서 우리의 손이 필요합니다
implemented the stuff there is just kind of painful so I'd probably use torture
아마 고문을 사용하는 것 때문에 그냥 가지 고통이 물건을 구현
maybe lasagna about semantic segmentation we want to classify every
어쩌면 우리는 모든 분류 할 의미 분할에 대해 라자냐
pixel right so here we want to read an input image and instead of giving a
우리는 입력 영상을 읽을 수와 대신을주는 바로 그래서 여기 화소를
label to the whole output image we want to label every pixel independently ok
우리가 독립적으로 확인 모든 픽셀에 라벨을 할 전체 출력 이미지에 레이블을
that's good so again my thought process was that we need a preteen model here
그 좋은 그렇게 다시 내 생각 과정은 우리가 여기 초반 이었죠 모델을 필요로했다입니다
most likely and hear that we're talking about kind of a weird use case for you
대부분 우리는 당신을 위해 이상한 사용 케이스의 종류에 대해 얘기 듣고
might need to define some of our own project so if this layer happens to
이 레이어가 발생, 그래서 만약 우리 자신의 프로젝트의 일부를 정의 할 필요가 있습니다
exist in cafe they would be a good fit otherwise what's the radar self and
그들은 레이더 자체의 다른 어떤 잘 맞는 것 카페에 존재
writing this thing ourself seems least 10 points for each object detection no
해결할없이 각 객체 검출을 위해 최소 10 점을 보이​​는이 일을 작성
idea
생각
yes ok kathy is an idea so my thought process again we're looking at preteen
예 확인 캐시는 생각이 나의 생각 과정을 다시 우리가 초반 이었죠보고있는 것입니다
models so we need cafe
모델은 그래서 우리는 카페 필요
torch or lasagna we actually could with the texting you could need a lot of
토치 또는 라자냐 우리는 실제로 문자 메시지로 당신이 많이 필요 할 수 있습니다
funky imperative code that it might be possible to put in a computation
그것은 할 수 있습니다 펑키 필수적 코드는 계산에 넣어
aircraft but seems scary to me so cafe + python is is 11 choice that some of the
11 선택이 카페 + 파이썬이 때문에 항공기하지만 나에게 무서운 것 같다의 일부가
spring we talked about actually went this route and I've actually done a
우리가에 대한 이야기​​ 봄 실제로이 길을 갔고, 나는 실제로 일을했습니다
similar project like this and I chose torch and it worked out good for me but
이 같은 유사 프로젝트와 나는 횃불을 선택하고 나를 위해 좋은 밖으로 일을하지만,
if you want to language modeling like you wanna do funky are intense and you
당신은 언어 모델링하려는 경우 펑키이 강렬 할 싶어하고 당신처럼
want to play with the recurrence role torch what do you guys thing yeah I
너희들의 일을 어떻게 재발 역할 토치와 함께 놀고 싶어 내가 네
would actually not used torture this at all so here if we just wanted to
우리가 원한다면 사실이 전혀 그래서 여기에 고문을 사용하지 않을 것
language modeling and do funky kind of recurrence relationships then we're not
언어 모델링과는 우리가하지 않은 재발 관계의 펑키 종류의 일을
talking about images at all this just untaxed so we don't need any pre-trial
이 모든 단지 비과세의 이미지에 대해 이야기하는 것은 그래서 우리는 어떤 사전 시험이 필요하지 않습니다
models and we really want to play with this recurrence relationship and easily
모델과 우리가 정말 쉽게 재발 관계와 놀고 싶어
work with our current networks so there I think that maybe fee on all returns
내가 생각하는 거기 때문에 현재 네트워크에서 작동하는 모든 반환에 아마 수수료
are flow might be a good choice if you want to implement batch norm
당신이 배치 표준을 구현하려는 경우입니다 흐름은 좋은 선택이 될 수 있습니다
ok ok slides sorry about that right so here if you wanna if you want to rely on
당신이에 의존 할 경우 싶다면 확인 확인 그래서 여기에 그 권리 미안 슬라이드
if you don't drive the gradient yourself and you could rely on these
당신은 그라데이션을 직접 운전하지 않는 당신은이에 의존 할 수 있다면
computational craft things like flow but because of the way that those things
흐름처럼하지만 방식 때문에의 계산 공예 것들 그 것들
work as you saw on homework for passion or you can actually simplify the
당신이 열정 숙제에서 본대로 작동하거나 실제로을 단순화 할 수 있습니다
gradient quite a lot and I'm not sure if these computational craft frameworks
꽤 많은 그라데이션 나는 확실하지 않다 이러한 계산 공예 프레임 워크 경우
would correctly simplify the gradient down to this makes efficient form
이 효율적인 양식을 만드는까지 제대로 그라데이션을 단순화 것
question
문제
I think I thought the question is how easily is at how easy is it to come by
나는 질문이 구하기하는 방법 쉬운에 얼마나 쉽게입니다 생각 생각
in like a torch model with a piano model and I think it seems painful but at
피아노 모델 횃불 모델 같은과 나는 고통스러운 듯 보이지만에서 생각
least in fiato you can use lasagna tick tick access and preteen models so
fiato에서 적어도 당신은 라자냐 틱 틱 액세스 등 초반 이었죠 모델을 사용할 수 있습니다
fucking together a lasagna model is something else I think theoretically
빌어 먹을 함께 라자냐 모델은 뭔가 다른 내가 이론적으로 생각하다
maybe should be easier so here if you want if you have some like really really
당신이 원하는 경우에 당신이 진짜 진짜 좋아해 몇 가지가 있다면 아마 그래서 여기에 쉽게해야한다
good knowledge about how how exactly you want the backward pass to be computed
정확히 어떻게 당신이 뒤로 패스를 할 방법에 대한 좋은 지식은 계산한다
and you want to implement it yourself to be efficient than you probably won't use
당신은 당신이 아마 사용하지 않습니다보다 효율적으로 스스로를 구현하려는
torch you can just implement that backup ask yourself so make recommendations on
토치 당신은 너무에 추천을 자신에게 물어 해당 백업을 구현할 수 있습니다
frameworks are that if you just wanna do feature feature extraction or maybe
프레임 워크는 당신은 싶어 아마 기능의 특징 추출을 할 경우, 또는
fine-tuning of existing models or just transferred of a vanilla straightforward
기존 모델의 미세 조정하거나 간단 바닐라의 전송
task then Cafe is probably the right way to go it's really easy to use you don't
작업은 다음 카페 아마 그렇지 사용하기 정말 쉽게 갈 수있는 올바른 방법이다
have to write any code if you want to work around with preteen models but
당신이 초반 이었죠 모델 주위에 작업 할 경우 임의의 코드를 작성해야하지만,
maybe do weird stuff with preteen models and not just fine to Phnom Penh you
어쩌면 프놈펜 당신에게 잘을 초반 이었죠 모델 이상한 물건을하고 있지
might have a better job in lasagna or torch is there it's easier to kind of
라자냐 또는 토치의 더 나은 일을 할 수도 있습니다 것은 가지를에 쉽게있다
mess with the structure of preteen models if you want to if you really
초반 이었죠 모델의 구조와 혼란 당신은 당신이 만약 정말로를 원하는 경우
really want to write your own layers for whatever reason and you don't think you
정말 어떤 이유로 자신의 레이어를 작성하려는 당신은 당신을 생각하지 않는다
can easily fit into these computational crafts then probably should use torch if
쉽게 이러한 계산 공예에 들어갈 수있는 것은 다음 아마도 경우 토치를 사용한다
you really want to use our intense and maybe other types of fancy things that
당신은 정말 멋진 일 우리의 강렬하고 어쩌면 다른 유형을 사용하려면 그
depend on the computational graph then probably talk then maybe fee on all
계산 그래프에 따라 다음 아마에 어쩌면 요금을 이야기
returns are low also if you have a gigantic model and you need to
당신이 거대한 모델이있는 경우 수익률도 낮은이고, 당신이 필요
distribute across an entire cluster and you have access to Google's internal
전체 클러스터에서 배포하고 구글의 내부에 액세스 할 수 있습니다
code base then you should use her flow
코드베이스는 그녀 흐름을 사용해야합니다
although hopefully that like I said that part will be released for the rest of us
내가 말했듯이 그 부분은 우리의 나머지 부분에 대한 발표 될 예정이다 희망이 있다고하지만,
soon so that's also if you wanna use tents are bored and you got a slow so
당신 싶어 사용 텐트가 지루해하는 경우 곧 있도록도 그리고 당신이 너무 느린있어
that's that's pretty much my my overview my quick whirlwind tour of all the
즉, 그 모든의 꽤 많이 내 내 개요 내 빠른 회오리 바람 투어의의
frameworks so any any last minute questions questions questions about
에 대한 프레임 워크 어떤 그래서 어떤 마지막 순간 질문 질문 질문
speed so there's actually a really nice page that compares some speed
그래서 약간의 속도를 비교하는 정말 좋은 페이지가 실제로 거기에 속도
benchmark speed of all the different frameworks and right now the one that
벤치 마크 모든 다른 프레임 워크의 속도와 지금 한 그
wins is none of these The one that wins is this thing called me on from Nirvana
승리 승리이 하나 하나도없는 것은이 일이 열반에서 저를 불려
systems so these guys have actually written these guys are crazy they
이 사람이 실제로이 녀석을 쓴 있도록 시스템은 미친 그들
actually wrote their own custom assembler for g4 and video hardware they
실제로 G4 및 비디오 하드웨어에 대한 자신의 정의 어셈블러를 쓴 사람들
were not happy with like and videos
같은과 동영상에 만족하지 않았다
toolchain they reverse engineer the hardware and rotor on a similar and then
툴체인 그들은 다음 유사한의 하드웨어와 회 전자를 리버스 엔지니어링
implemented all these kernels in assembly themselves so these guys are
어셈블리에서 구현 된 모든 커널 자체가 그래서이 사람들이
crazy and their stuff is really really fast so they're actually there is there
미친 실제로이 존재하고, 그래서 자신의 물건은 정말 정말 빠릅니다
stuff is actually the fastest right now but I've never really used their I've
물건은 지금 실제로 가장 빠른하지만 난 정말 내가 그들의했습니다 사용한 적이
never really used their framework myself and I think it's a little less common
결코 정말 자신의 프레임 워크 나 자신을 사용하고 난 좀 덜 일반적인 생각
these although for the ones that are using CUDA and the speed is roughly the
CUDA와 속도를 사용하는 사람에 대한하지만 이들은 대략이다
same right now I think 10 surplus quite a bit slower than the others for some
같은 지금 나는 약간의 다른 사람보다 10 여분 상당히 느린 생각
silly reasons that I think will be cleaned up in subsequent releases but at
내가 생각하는 어리석은 이유는 후속 릴리스에서 만에 정리한다
least fundamentally there's no reason you should be should should should be
적어도 근본적으로 당신이해야해야해야해야 할 이유가 없습니다
slower than others
다른 사람보다 느린
you people are picking up rifles
당신의 사람들은 소총을 집어 들고있다
alright
다 좋아
that that's actually not crazy there are quite a few for quite a few teams last
즉 실제로 미친 아니에요 대부분의 팀이 마지막에 대한 꽤있다
year that actually use a sign like Oprah projects and it was fine
올해이 실제로 오프라 프로젝트와 같은 기호를 사용하고 그것을 잘했다
yeah I should also mention that there are other frameworks
그래 나는 또한 다른 프레임 워크가 있다는 것을 언급해야한다
I just think these are the peace for the most common question
난 그냥이 가장 일반적인 질문에 대한 평화를 생각한다
so the question is about grabbing and torch so torch actually has and I Python
그래서 질문은 잡아 토치 토치가 실제로있다, 그래서 내가 파이썬에 관한 것입니다
colonel you can actually use on my torch notebooks that's kind of cool and
대령 실제로 종류의 멋진 나의 성화 노트북에서 사용할 수 있으며,
actually you can actually do some simple grabbing a night or two notebooks but in
실제로 당신은 실제로 밤 또는 두 개의 노트북 만에 잡는 몇 가지 간단한 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다
practice what I usually do is dump my data run my torch model dump the data
난 보통 내 데이터가 내 토치 모델은 데이터를 덤프 실행 덤프됩니다 않는 것을 실천
even to JSON HDL 5 and in visualizing in Python which is a little bit little bit
심지어 JSON의 HDL 5 파이썬에서 시각화에 조금 조금이다
painful but you can just get the job done
고통스러운하지만 당신은 작업이 완료 얻을 수 있습니다
the question is whether tenser bored lets you dump the raw data you can put
문제는 지루 tenser 당신이 넣을 수 있습니다 당신은 원시 데이터를 덤프 할 수 있는지 여부입니다
yourself there actually they're actually dumping all this stuff into some log
거기에 자신이 실제로 그들은 실제로 일부 로그에 모든 물건을 덤핑하고
files in a temp directory I'm not sure how easy those are sparse but you could
임시 디렉토리에있는 파일 나는 사람들은 드문 드문 얼마나 쉽게 잘 모르겠어요하지만 당신은 할 수
try it could be easy or not I'm not sure question the question is whether there
쉽게 할 수있는 시도하거나 나는 문제가 있는지 있는지 질문하지 아니에요
are other third party tool some of the tensor board for modern networks there
이 현대적인 네트워크를위한 텐서 보드의 다른 타사 도구입니다
might be some out there but I've never really used them I just read my own in
거기서 몇 가지있을 수 있습니다하지만 난 정말 그들을 사용한 적이 난 그냥 내 자신을 읽기
the past any other questions
과거 다른 질문
alright I think I think that's it
확실히 나는 그게 생각 생각